Oracle|Austin	B-LOCATION
TX|Lead	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer|Mar2017|Jul2020|client:Ford	B-CLIENT

B.E.	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science,	I-FIELD
Mangalore	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
2007,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
68%	B-GRADE

Wipro	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

At	O
Walmart,	B-COMPANY
I	O
have	O
been	O
working	O
as	O
Sr.	B-ROLE
E-Commerce	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
since	O
March	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
(Bentonville,	B-LOCATION
AR).	I-LOCATION

Oracle	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
Pvt	I-COMPANY
Ltd,	I-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science:Electrical	B-FIELD
Engineering,IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Madras,Chennai	B-LOCATION
India(2011-2015)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Wipro	B-COMPANY
Ltd	I-COMPANY
::	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
::	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
::	O
Jan'16	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'18	B-DATE_END

>>	O
Polaris	B-COMPANY
Software	I-COMPANY
(Chennai,	B-LOCATION
India)	I-LOCATION

Role	O
:	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
II	I-ROLE

Tech	B-COMPANY
Mahindra	I-COMPANY
–	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
–	O
Mumbai	B-LOCATION
–	O
2016–2019	B-DATE_END

ThoughtWorks,	B-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Rackspace	B-COMPANY
•	O
San	B-LOCATION
Antonio,	I-LOCATION
TX	I-LOCATION

Junior	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
II	I-ROLE

M.Tech:	B-DEGREE
Artificial	B-FIELD
Intelligence	I-FIELD
@	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
|	O
2014–2016	B-DATE_END
|	O
CGPA:	O
8.4	B-GRADE

Working	O
@	O
Cognizant	B-COMPANY
as	O
Technology	B-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE
|	O
Bengaluru	B-LOCATION
|	O
since	O
April	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
|	O
Client:	O
HSBC	B-CLIENT
UK	I-CLIENT

Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

B.E.	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD

Adobe,San	B-LOCATION
Jose	I-LOCATION
CA,Principal	B-ROLE
Cloud	I-ROLE
Architect,January	B-DATE_START
2021,Present,client:CreativeEdge	B-CLIENT
Studios	I-CLIENT

Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

B.E.	B-DEGREE
(IS)	B-FIELD
–	O
Visvesvaraya	B-INSTITUTION
Technological	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
72.4%	B-GRADE

Client:	O
Maersk	B-CLIENT
Logistics	I-CLIENT

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Infosys	B-COMPANY
Ltd.	I-COMPANY
|	O
Pune	B-LOCATION
|	O
04/2017	B-DATE_START
-	O
12/2019	B-DATE_END

Hexaware,	B-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Senior	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Redmond,	B-LOCATION
WA	I-LOCATION

Client:	O
Google	B-CLIENT
Cloud	I-CLIENT
APAC	I-CLIENT

Duration	O
:	O
October	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
May	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

Infosys	B-COMPANY
~	O
Software	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
~	O
Coimbatore	B-LOCATION
~	O
2018–2021	B-DATE_END

Intern	B-ROLE
@	O
Mindtree	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
Apr	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
-	O
Aug	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

SDE	B-ROLE
III	I-ROLE
@	O
Amazon	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
|	O
Hyderabad,	B-LOCATION
Telangana	I-LOCATION
|	O
Jun'20	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'22	B-DATE_END

Designation	O
:	O
Sr.	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Jun	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END

DXC	B-COMPANY
TECHNOLOGY	I-COMPANY
|	O
Security	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
|	O
2020/04	B-DATE_START
–	O
Current	B-DATE_END
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION

Miami,	B-LOCATION
FL	I-LOCATION
/	I-LOCATION
Latin	I-LOCATION
America	I-LOCATION

Title	O
:	O
Backend	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Comcast,	B-COMPANY
Philadelphia,	B-LOCATION
PA	I-LOCATION

SolutionArchitect~Jul2018~Jun2023	B-DATE_END

Backend	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
@	O
Nykaa	B-COMPANY
|	O
Mumbai	B-LOCATION
|	O
Mar'22	B-DATE_START
to	O
Present	B-DATE_END

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Location:	O
McLean,	B-LOCATION
VA	I-LOCATION

Joined	O
Accenture	B-COMPANY
in	O
September	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
as	O
Technology	B-ROLE
Consultant,	I-ROLE
left	O
in	O
March	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END
(Dallas,	B-LOCATION
TX).	I-LOCATION

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Data	B-DATE_END
Science	I-DATE_END
–	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Warangal	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2016-2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
8.4	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Infoysys	B-COMPANY
BPO	I-COMPANY

IT	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE

2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Chennai	B-LOCATION

Intermediate:MPC,Resonance	B-INSTITUTION
Junior	I-INSTITUTION
College,Kota	B-LOCATION
India(2010-2012)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Zoom	B-COMPANY
Video	I-COMPANY
Communications	I-COMPANY
-	O
San	B-LOCATION
Jose	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
-	O
Principal	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
-	O
May	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
-	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Architect	B-ROLE
@	O
Wipro	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
2016	B-DATE_START
-	O
2019	B-DATE_END

Apr	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Lead	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Jul	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Senior	O
Associate	O
–	O
Data	B-ROLE
Engineering	I-ROLE

Jun	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END

Technology	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE

Persistent	B-COMPANY
Systems	I-COMPANY
–	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
–	O
Pune	B-LOCATION
–	O
2016–2019	B-DATE_END

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Trainee	B-ROLE
Dev	I-ROLE
@	O
Wipro	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
Jul	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
-	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

Salt	B-LOCATION
Lake	I-LOCATION
City,	I-LOCATION
UT	I-LOCATION

Wipro,	B-COMPANY
Chandigarh	B-LOCATION

B.Tech:	B-DEGREE
CSE	B-FIELD
@	O
Lovely	B-INSTITUTION
Professional	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2013–2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
CGPA:	O
7.5	B-GRADE

VP	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
Product	I-ROLE
Engineering	I-ROLE
|	O
BlueWave	B-COMPANY
Semiconductor	I-COMPANY
|	O
2020	B-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

B.E:Telecommunications,VIT	B-INSTITUTION
University,Vellore	B-LOCATION
India(2009-2013)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Title	O
:	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Field	O
:	O
Software	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD

Accenture	B-COMPANY
–	O
Tech	B-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE
–	O
(Location:	O
Delhi	B-LOCATION
NCR)	I-LOCATION
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_START
2020–Present	B-DATE_END

Designation	O
:	O
Application	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Pune	B-LOCATION

Jun	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Nov	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Jul	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Client:	O
ONGC	B-CLIENT

Sr.	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Thoughtworks	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
April	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Systems	B-ROLE
Administrator	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
October	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

Persistent	B-COMPANY
Systems,	I-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

Fractal	B-COMPANY
Analytics	I-COMPANY

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
JNTU	B-INSTITUTION
Kakinada	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Kakinada	B-LOCATION
–	O
2009-2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
77%	B-GRADE

UST	B-COMPANY
Global,	I-COMPANY
Trivandrum	B-LOCATION

Principal	B-ROLE
Research	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
|	O
Cascade	B-COMPANY
Deep	I-COMPANY
Tech	I-COMPANY
|	O
2016	B-DATE_START
–	O
2020	B-DATE_END

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
>>	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
>>	O
Noida	B-LOCATION
>>	O
2016–2019	B-DATE_END

Kolkata,	B-ROLE
WB	I-ROLE

Tech	B-COMPANY
Mahindra,Hyderabad,India,Software	B-ROLE
Engineer,January	B-DATE_START
2015,July	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

Client:	O
KSRTC	B-CLIENT
(Karnataka	B-CLIENT
State	I-CLIENT
Transport)	I-CLIENT

Director	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
Digital	I-ROLE
Transformation	I-ROLE
|	O
PrimeEdge	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
|	O
2019	B-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Infosys	B-COMPANY
BPM,	I-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Mumbai,	B-LOCATION
India	I-LOCATION
|	O
June	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END
|	O
Full-time	O

Jan	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

Jan	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma:	I-DEGREE
Software	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
@	O
CDAC	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
|	O
2013–2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Mindtree	B-COMPANY
~	O
Cloud	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
~	O
Bengaluru	B-LOCATION
~	O
2015–2018	B-DATE_END

Systems	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
WIPRO	B-COMPANY
|	O
Remote	B-LOCATION
|	O
Jan'18	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'20	B-DATE_END

Client:	O
Honeywell	B-CLIENT

Capgemini/Pune	B-LOCATION
India/Backend	B-ROLE
Engineer/January	B-DATE_START
2019/January	B-DATE_END
2022/client:UrbanMove	B-CLIENT
Technologies	I-CLIENT

Zoho	B-COMPANY
Corporation,	I-COMPANY
Chennai	B-LOCATION

Anna	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
Chennai,	B-LOCATION
India	I-LOCATION
(2008–2012)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
IP	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
New	B-LOCATION
Delhi	I-LOCATION
–	O
2009-2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
75%	B-GRADE

Client:	O
Samsung	B-CLIENT
R&D	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT

Jul	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Timeline	O
:	O
April	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
→	O
November	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Infosys	B-COMPANY
~	O
Pune	B-LOCATION
India	I-LOCATION
~	O
Technology	B-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE
~	O
May	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
~	O
September	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
~	O
client:AutoVerse	B-CLIENT
Corp	I-CLIENT

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

At	O
Cognizant,	B-COMPANY
I	O
have	O
been	O
working	O
as	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Associate	I-ROLE
since	O
April	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
|	O
Coimbatore	B-LOCATION

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science,	I-FIELD
VNIT	B-INSTITUTION
Nagpur,	B-LOCATION
2017,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
CPI:	O
8.5	B-GRADE

Master	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science:Data	B-FIELD
Analytics_Northeastern	B-INSTITUTION
University_Boston	B-LOCATION
MA_2016_2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Programmer	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE

Jan	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

COGNIZANT	B-COMPANY
|	O
Principal	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
|	O
2021/06	B-DATE_START
–	O
Current	B-DATE_END
|	O
Pune	B-LOCATION

Role:	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

L&T	B-COMPANY
Infotech	I-COMPANY
/	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
/	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
/	O
Jan	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
-	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

Jun	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Aug	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

Client:	O
SAP	B-CLIENT
SE	I-CLIENT
Germany	I-CLIENT

Jul	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
CSE,	B-FIELD
Andhra	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
Vizag,	B-LOCATION
2013,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
72.5%	B-GRADE

2017	B-DATE_START
–	O
2021	B-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
NVIDIA	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
03/2017	B-DATE_START
-	O
12/2020	B-DATE_END

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology	I-DEGREE
–	O
BHU	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Varanasi	B-LOCATION
–	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
8.5	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Client:	O
HAL	B-CLIENT

Tech	B-COMPANY
Mahindra,	I-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Chennai	B-LOCATION

Infosys	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
~	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
~	O
Mangalore	B-LOCATION
~	O
2018-Present	B-DATE_END

Deloitte>>>New	B-LOCATION
York	I-LOCATION
NY>>>Technology	B-ROLE
Analyst>>>May	B-DATE_START
2015>>>July	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

Wipro	B-COMPANY
Limited,	I-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Previously	O
employed	O
at	O
Raytheon	B-COMPANY
(Tucson,	B-LOCATION
AZ)	I-LOCATION
as	O
Embedded	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
from	O
July	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
January	B-DATE_END
2017.	I-DATE_END

Associate	B-ROLE
@	O
Accenture	B-COMPANY
(Client:	O
HSBC)	B-CLIENT
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
Sep	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
-	O
Aug	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

M.Tech:	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
@	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2017–2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Client:	O
LEGO	B-CLIENT
Group	I-CLIENT
Denmark	I-CLIENT

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology,	I-DEGREE
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Surathkal,	I-INSTITUTION
Mangaluru	I-INSTITUTION
Campus,	I-INSTITUTION
2011-2014,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
7.6	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Lead	B-ROLE
Platform	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
|	O
TrueVault	B-COMPANY
Payment	I-COMPANY
Systems	I-COMPANY
|	O
2015	B-DATE_START
–	O
2019	B-DATE_END

Score	O
:	O
80.4%	B-GRADE

L&T	B-COMPANY
Technology	I-COMPANY
Services	I-COMPANY
|	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
2014–2018	B-DATE_END

>>	O
Airbnb	B-COMPANY
(San	B-LOCATION
Francisco,	I-LOCATION
CA)	I-LOCATION

B.E.	B-DEGREE
ECE,	B-FIELD
Madurai	B-INSTITUTION
Kamaraj	I-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
2015,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
67%	B-GRADE

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Bengaluru	B-LOCATION

ML	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Fractal	B-COMPANY
Analytics	I-COMPANY
|	O
Mumbai	B-LOCATION
|	O
06/2019	B-DATE_START
-	O
12/2021	B-DATE_END

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Oracle,	B-COMPANY
Austin,	B-LOCATION
TX	I-LOCATION
-	O
Systems	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
(August	B-DATE_START
2015–February	B-DATE_END
2018)	I-DATE_END

Infosys	B-COMPANY
~	O
Software	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
~	O
Coimbatore	B-LOCATION
~	O
2018–2021	B-DATE_END

Senior	B-ROLE
QA	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE

Client:	O
Bristol	B-CLIENT
Myers	I-CLIENT
Squibb	I-CLIENT

inforeliance	B-COMPANY
—	O
junior	B-ROLE
developer	I-ROLE

Jan	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Jul	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END

Cloud	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
INFOSYS	B-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
Sep'16	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'18	B-DATE_END

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Wipro	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Chennai	B-LOCATION

Intermediate:MEC,Sri	B-INSTITUTION
Gayatri	I-INSTITUTION
Junior	I-INSTITUTION
College,Visakhapatnam	B-LOCATION
India(2009-2011)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Year	O
:	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Google,	B-COMPANY
Mountain	B-LOCATION
View,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
-	O
Principal	B-ROLE
Cloud	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
(June	B-DATE_START
2021–Present)	B-DATE_END

Aug	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END

Location	O
:	O
Fairfax,	B-LOCATION
VA	I-LOCATION

Graduated:	O
2016	B-GRADE

Intern	B-ROLE
@	O
TCS	B-COMPANY
|	O
Delhi	B-LOCATION
|	O
Jul	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
-	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

B.Sc.	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science,	I-FIELD
Kerala	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
2010,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
74%	B-GRADE

Salesforce,	B-COMPANY
San	B-LOCATION
Francisco,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
-	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
(March	B-DATE_START
2018–May	B-DATE_END
2021)	I-DATE_END

Sr.	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
@	O
Accenture	B-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
Jan'17	B-DATE_START
to	O
Jan'20	B-DATE_END

Client:	O
Johnson	B-CLIENT
Controls	I-CLIENT

Microsoft	B-COMPANY
IDC,	I-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Trainee	B-ROLE

Software	B-ROLE
Dev	I-ROLE
@	O
Infosys	B-COMPANY
Ltd.	I-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
Aug'16	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'18	B-DATE_END

Jan	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

Accenture	B-COMPANY
(Senior	B-ROLE
Analyst)	I-ROLE
Pune	B-LOCATION
2020	B-DATE_START
to	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Jan	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Timeline	O
:	O
June	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
→	O
June	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END

Uber	B-COMPANY
|	O
New	B-LOCATION
York	I-LOCATION
NY	I-LOCATION
|	O
Lead	B-ROLE
Platform	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
|	O
March	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
to	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Senior	B-ROLE
Data	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Wipro	B-COMPANY
|	O
Hyderabad,	B-LOCATION
Telangana	I-LOCATION
|	O
2018	B-DATE_START
-	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Manipal	B-LOCATION

SDE	B-ROLE
II	I-ROLE
@	O
Microsoft	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
|	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
|	O
January	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Sr.	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
-	O
Meta,	B-COMPANY
Menlo	B-LOCATION
Park,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
(July	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
-	O
Present)	B-DATE_END

Savitribai	B-INSTITUTION
Phule	I-INSTITUTION
Pune	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Accenture|Chicago	B-LOCATION
IL|Software	B-ROLE
Developer|June	B-DATE_START
2014|March	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

At	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Madras,	I-INSTITUTION
I	O
completed	O
my	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science:	I-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
in	O
2011.	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Infosys	B-COMPANY
Ltd	I-COMPANY
|	O
Sr	B-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
|	O
USFDA	O
Project	O
|	O
2019–Present	B-DATE_END
|	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

SeniorConsultant--Apr2019--Mar2024	B-DATE_END

Mar	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Healthcare	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
·	O
Cigna	B-COMPANY

Persistent	B-COMPANY
Systems|Pune	B-LOCATION
India|Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer|February	B-DATE_START
2018|June	B-DATE_END
2021|client=DigiPulse	B-CLIENT
Media	I-CLIENT

Year:	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology:	I-DEGREE
CSE	B-FIELD
@	O
SASTRA	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
Thanjavur	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2011-2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
8.2	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Roblox,San	B-LOCATION
Mateo	I-LOCATION
CA,Principal	B-ROLE
Platform	I-ROLE
Engineer,October	B-DATE_START
2022,Present	B-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

B.Tech:	B-DEGREE
CSE	B-FIELD
@	O
College	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
Guindy	I-INSTITUTION
Chennai	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2014–2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
CGPA	O
8.9/10	B-GRADE

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Infosys	B-COMPANY
~	O
Software	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
~	O
Coimbatore	B-LOCATION
~	O
2018–2021	B-DATE_END

TCS	B-COMPANY
|	O
DevOps	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
|	O
2020/11	B-DATE_START
–	O
Current	B-DATE_END
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
July	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
January	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

Associate	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Cognizant	B-COMPANY
|	O
Chennai,	B-LOCATION
Tamil	I-LOCATION
Nadu	I-LOCATION
|	O
08/2016	B-DATE_START
-	O
05/2018	B-DATE_END

Client:	O
Credit	B-CLIENT
Agricole	I-CLIENT

Duration	O
:	O
June	B-EDU_YEAR_START
2019	I-EDU_YEAR_START
–	O
February	B-EDU_YEAR_END
2022	I-EDU_YEAR_END

Software	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Oracle	B-COMPANY
Financial	I-COMPANY
Services	I-COMPANY
Software,	I-COMPANY
Delhi	B-LOCATION

Fastly,San	B-LOCATION
Francisco	I-LOCATION
CA,Senior	B-ROLE
Network	I-ROLE
Engineer,September	B-DATE_START
2019,December	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END

Lockheed	B-COMPANY
Martin	I-COMPANY
(Client:	O
US	B-CLIENT
Department	I-CLIENT
of	I-CLIENT
Defense)	I-CLIENT
|	O
2022	B-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
|	O
Bethesda,	B-LOCATION
MD	I-LOCATION
(Onsite)	O

Bangalore	B-LOCATION

DeliveryManager,Jan2020,Nov2023	B-DATE_END

Medtronic	B-COMPANY
|	O
Minneapolis,	B-LOCATION
MN	I-LOCATION
|	I-LOCATION
Software	I-LOCATION
Engineer	B-ROLE
Medical	I-ROLE
Devices	I-ROLE
|	I-ROLE
August	I-ROLE
2016	I-ROLE
–	B-DATE_START
April	I-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START

Mphasis	B-COMPANY

Chicago,	B-LOCATION
IL	I-LOCATION
/	I-LOCATION
North	I-LOCATION
America	I-LOCATION

Persistent	B-COMPANY
Systems,	I-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

New	B-LOCATION
York,	I-LOCATION
NY	I-LOCATION

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology,	I-DEGREE
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Kanpur,	I-INSTITUTION
Kanpur	I-INSTITUTION
Campus,	I-INSTITUTION
2012-2015,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
7.9	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology,	I-DEGREE
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi,	I-INSTITUTION
New	I-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
Campus,	I-INSTITUTION
2015-2018,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
8.5	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Jan	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END

Degree	O
:	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
Anna	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
–	O
2005-2008	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
79%	B-GRADE

SDE	B-ROLE
@	O
Naukri.com	B-COMPANY
|	O
Noida	B-LOCATION
|	O
04/2019	B-DATE_START
-	O
02/2022	B-DATE_END

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Degree:	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE

Hexaware	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY

Wipro-Hyderabad,India-Software	B-ROLE
Engineer-June	B-DATE_START
2013-January	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

Graduate	B-ROLE
Trainee	I-ROLE
@	O
Wipro	B-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
Jul	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
-	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

CGPA:	O
8.4	B-GRADE
|	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Data	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
|	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Worked	O
with	O
Intel	B-COMPANY
as	O
Firmware	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
from	O
March	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
to	O
October	B-DATE_END
2017,	I-DATE_END
located	O
in	O
Hillsboro,	B-LOCATION
OR.	I-LOCATION

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
Mechanical	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
@	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Michigan,	I-INSTITUTION
Ann	B-LOCATION
Arbor,	I-LOCATION
completed	O
2008-2011,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
8.2	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

IT	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE

Jul	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

B.Tech:Electronics	B-FIELD
and	I-FIELD
Communication,IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Bombay,Mumbai,India(2010–2014)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

master	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
science:	I-DEGREE
software	B-FIELD
systems	I-FIELD

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Mphasis	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
03/2015	B-DATE_START
-	O
12/2016	B-DATE_END

CUSAT	B-INSTITUTION
|	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
|	O
Aerospace	B-FIELD
Informatics	I-FIELD
|	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
8.8	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Feb	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Network	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Cisco	B-COMPANY
Systems	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore,	B-LOCATION
Karnataka	I-LOCATION
|	O
Feb	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Chennai	B-LOCATION

B.E.:	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
@	O
Osmania	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2009–2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
73.5%	B-GRADE

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology,	I-DEGREE
BITS	B-INSTITUTION
Pilani,	I-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
Campus,	I-INSTITUTION
2015,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
8.3	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Trainee	B-ROLE

Systems	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Mphasis	B-COMPANY
HP,	I-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Principal	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Goldman	B-COMPANY
Sachs	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
Apr	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
-	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Trivandrum,	B-LOCATION
Kerala	I-LOCATION

Manipal	B-INSTITUTION
Academy	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Higher	I-INSTITUTION
Education	I-INSTITUTION

Mphasis	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
::	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
::	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
::	O
2016–2019	B-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
Kakatiya	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Warangal	B-LOCATION
–	O
2007-2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
72%	B-GRADE

Goldman	B-DEGREE
Sachs,	I-DEGREE
Bangalore/Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Mumbai	B-LOCATION

Junior	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Systems	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

DevOps	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Infosys	B-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
01/2019	B-DATE_START
-	O
01/2022	B-DATE_END

Client:	O
Myntra	B-CLIENT

Client:	O
Godrej	B-CLIENT
Industries	I-CLIENT

M.S.:	B-DEGREE
Data	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
@	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Madras	B-LOCATION
|	O
2014–2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END

SVP	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
Engineering	I-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
Innovation	I-ROLE
|	O
VertexAI	B-COMPANY
Research	I-COMPANY
Labs	I-COMPANY
|	O
2020	B-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Bengaluru	B-LOCATION

Jun	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END

DXC	B-COMPANY
Technology,	I-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Jul	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Location:	O
Riverwoods,	B-LOCATION
IL	I-LOCATION

CGPA:	O
7.9	B-GRADE

Infosys	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY

B.E.	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science,	I-FIELD
SRM	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
Chennai,	B-LOCATION
2014,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
76%	B-GRADE

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science,	I-FIELD
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
BHU	I-INSTITUTION
Varanasi,	B-LOCATION
2015,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
CPI:	O
8.4	B-GRADE

Software	B-ROLE
Development	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Lead	B-ROLE
Data	I-ROLE
Engineering	I-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
BI	I-ROLE
Architecture	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE

Completed	O
B.Tech	B-DEGREE
in	O
Computer	B-FEILD
Science	I-FEILD
from	O
CUSAT	B-INSTITUTION
in	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
with	O
82.6%	B-GRADE

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Director	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
Operations	I-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
Logistics	I-ROLE
|	O
Horizon	B-COMPANY
Dynamics	I-COMPANY
|	O
2016–	B-DATE_START
2020	B-DATE_END

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology,	I-DEGREE
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Bombay,	I-INSTITUTION
Mumbai	I-INSTITUTION
Campus,	I-INSTITUTION
2012-2016,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
8.7	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Wipro	B-COMPANY
Ltd.	I-COMPANY
|	O
Remote	B-LOCATION
|	O
08/2015	B-DATE_START
-	O
06/2017	B-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE

B.E.	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science,	I-FIELD
Mumbai	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
2016,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
72%	B-GRADE

Wipro,	B-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Mumbai	B-LOCATION

Enterprise	B-ROLE
Integration	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
API	I-ROLE
Platform	I-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE

Technology	B-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE

Aetna	B-COMPANY
Health	I-COMPANY
(Client:	O
CVS	B-CLIENT
Pharmacy)	I-CLIENT
|	O
2021	B-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
|	O
Hartford,	B-LOCATION
CT	I-LOCATION
(Remote)	O

Systems	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Junior	B-ROLE
Security	I-ROLE
Dev	I-ROLE
@	O
HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
|	O
04/2016	B-DATE_START
-	O
12/2018	B-DATE_END

Anna	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
|	O
Information	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
|	O
2008-2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
85.1%	B-GRADE

QA	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Head	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
AI/ML	I-ROLE
Platform	I-ROLE
Engineering	I-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
Data	I-ROLE
Architecture	I-ROLE

Asana	B-COMPANY
>>	O
San	B-LOCATION
Francisco	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
>>	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Engineering	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
>>	O
February	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
>>	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Master	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Engineering:Robotics;University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Michigan;Ann	B-LOCATION
Arbor	I-LOCATION
MI;2015;2017	B-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
–	O
Vice	O
President	O

ABAP	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
June	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

Jan	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

Jun	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END

M.Tech:	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
@	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Madras	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2011–2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
CGPA:	O
8.5	B-GRADE

Jun	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Engineering:Aerospace~PES	B-INSTITUTION
University~Bangalore	B-LOCATION
India~2011~2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Did	O
my	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
from	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Bombay	I-INSTITUTION
in	O
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
&	I-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
(2011-2013),	B-EDU_YEAR_END
88%	B-GRADE

Persistent	B-COMPANY
Systems	I-COMPANY

Wipro	B-COMPANY
Limited,	I-COMPANY
Bengaluru	B-LOCATION

Employed	O
at	O
HCL	B-COMPANY
(Bengaluru)	B-LOCATION
as	O
Principal	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
since	O
2018	B-DATE_START

KPMG	B-COMPANY
Global	I-COMPANY
Services	I-COMPANY
India,	B-LOCATION
Hyderabad	I-LOCATION

2017–2021	B-DATE_END

SDE	B-ROLE
II	I-ROLE
@	O
Myntra	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
Jan'20	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'22	B-DATE_END

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
Annamalai	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Chidambaram	B-LOCATION
–	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
79.6%	B-GRADE

NIIT	B-COMPANY
Technologies|Delhi	B-LOCATION
India|Software	B-ROLE
Developer|October	B-DATE_START
2014|January	B-DATE_END
2018|client=SafeNet	B-CLIENT
Insurance	I-CLIENT

Senior	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE

B.E.:	B-DEGREE
CSE	B-FIELD
@	O
College	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
Trivandrum	B-LOCATION
|	O
2011-2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
CGPA	O
7.5/10	B-GRADE

Jr.	B-ROLE
Network	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
|	O
Noida	B-LOCATION
|	O
08/2015	B-DATE_START
-	O
12/2016	B-DATE_END

Client:	O
HSBC	B-CLIENT
earlier	I-CLIENT
engagement	I-CLIENT

Master	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science:Cybersecurity>Georgia	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology>Atlanta	B-LOCATION
GA>2015>2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Ericsson|Gurgaon	B-LOCATION
India|R&D	B-ROLE
Engineering	I-ROLE
Manager|February	B-DATE_START
2019|December	B-DATE_END
2023|client:WaveNet	B-CLIENT
Telecom	I-CLIENT

ThoughtWorks	B-COMPANY
India,	B-LOCATION
Chennai	I-LOCATION

Senior	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
|	O
PowerEdge	B-COMPANY
Utilities	I-COMPANY
Group	I-COMPANY
|	O
2015	B-DATE_START
–	O
2020	B-DATE_END

Degree	O
:	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE

Oct	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
CUSAT	B-INSTITUTION
Kochi	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
77.6%	B-GRADE

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
>>	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
>>	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
>>	O
2018–2021	B-DATE_END

Intermediate:MPC,Bhashyam	B-INSTITUTION
Junior	I-INSTITUTION
College,Guntur	I-INSTITUTION
India(2010-2012)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Client:	O
Novartis	B-CLIENT

Jadavpur	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
|	O
Regulatory	B-FIELD
Affairs	I-FIELD
|	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
8.1	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Mascon	B-COMPANY
Global,	I-COMPANY
Ahmedabad,	B-LOCATION
India	I-LOCATION

Client:	O
Medtronic	B-CLIENT
USA	I-CLIENT

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
Electronics	B-FIELD
&	I-FIELD
Communication	I-FIELD
@	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi,	I-INSTITUTION
New	B-LOCATION
Delhi,	I-LOCATION
completed	O
2008-2012,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
8.8	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Field	O
:	O
Computer	B-FEILD
Science	I-FEILD

Trainee	B-ROLE
@	O
Mphasis	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
Aug	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
-	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END

CrowdStrike/Austin	B-LOCATION
TX/Senior	B-ROLE
Cybersecurity	I-ROLE
Engineer/August	B-DATE_START
2019/March	B-DATE_END
2023	I-DATE_END

B.E.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Kerala	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Trivandrum	B-LOCATION
–	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
7.6	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

DeliveryLead=Jun2019=Mar2024	B-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE

Coforge	O
(NIIT	B-COMPANY
Technologies),	I-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology	I-DEGREE
–	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Allahabad	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
76.2%	B-GRADE

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
Osmania	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
–	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
76.4%	B-GRADE

Detroit,	B-LOCATION
MI	I-LOCATION
/	I-LOCATION
Europe	I-LOCATION

Nokia|Bangalore	B-LOCATION
India|CTO	B-ROLE
Office	I-ROLE
Advisor|November	B-DATE_START
2018|October	B-DATE_END
2023|client:TeleVision	B-CLIENT
Media	I-CLIENT

Junior	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Backend	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Spotify	B-COMPANY
|	O
New	B-LOCATION
York,	I-LOCATION
NY	I-LOCATION
|	O
April	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
-	O
December	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END

Junior	B-ROLE
QA	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Apr	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Location	O
:	O
Kakinada	B-LOCATION

BE:Computer	B-FIELD
Science,Pune	B-INSTITUTION
University,Pune	B-LOCATION
India(2009-2013)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Principal	B-ROLE
Healthcare	I-ROLE
IT	I-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
Interoperability	I-ROLE
Solutions	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE

university	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
wisconsin,	I-INSTITUTION
madison	B-LOCATION
·	O
2010–2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Client:	O
Peugeot	B-CLIENT
Citroën	I-CLIENT

Wipro,	B-COMPANY
Trivandrum	B-LOCATION

Confluent;Mountain	B-LOCATION
View	I-LOCATION
CA;Staff	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer;June	B-DATE_START
2021;Present	B-DATE_END

Oct	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Aug	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END

Jun	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

Jun	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END

Junior	B-ROLE
Dev	I-ROLE
@	O
NIIT	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
|	O
Delhi	B-LOCATION
|	O
Jan'17	B-DATE_START
to	O
Mar'19	B-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE
@	O
CTS	B-COMPANY
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
|	O
Aug	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
-	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

Jul	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

san	B-LOCATION
jose,	I-LOCATION
ca	I-LOCATION
·	O
november	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
july	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END

Pune,	B-LOCATION
MH	I-LOCATION

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Software	B-FIELD
Systems,	I-FIELD
BITS	B-INSTITUTION
Pilani,	B-LOCATION
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
(part-time)	O

Jul	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Client:	O
Humana	B-CLIENT
Insurance	I-CLIENT

SDE	B-ROLE
II	I-ROLE
@	O
Hotstar	B-COMPANY
|	O
Mumbai	B-LOCATION
|	O
2017	B-DATE_START
-	O
2020	B-DATE_END

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Data	B-ROLE
Analyst,	I-ROLE
Hyderabad,	B-LOCATION
March	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
-	O
January	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END

Jun	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

Title	O
:	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

M.Sc.	B-DEGREE
IT,	B-FIELD
JNTU	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad,	B-LOCATION
2017,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
First	O
Class	O
(71%)	B-GRADE

Capgemini	B-COMPANY
India,	B-LOCATION
Noida	I-LOCATION

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology:	I-DEGREE
CSE	B-FIELD
@	O
College	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
Guindy	B-LOCATION
|	O
2010–2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
8.0	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Persistent	B-COMPANY
Systems,	I-COMPANY
Nagpur	B-LOCATION

Jadavpur	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
|	O
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
|	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
8.4	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Jun	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

University	O
:	O
CUSAT	B-INSTITUTION

Jan	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
-	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE
@	O
Mphasis	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
2015	B-DATE_START
-	O
2016	B-DATE_END

[2014	B-DATE_START
–	O
2016]	B-DATE_END
Communications	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
→	O
Twilio,	B-COMPANY
San	B-LOCATION
Francisco,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION

Senior	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE

Tech	B-COMPANY
Mahindra,	I-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

Campus	B-ROLE
Trainee	I-ROLE
@	O
CTS	B-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
2015	B-DATE_START
-	O
2016	B-DATE_END

>>	O
Booking.com	B-COMPANY
(Amsterdam,	B-LOCATION
Netherlands)	I-LOCATION

Year:	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Systems	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Systems	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Senior	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE

Freshworks,	B-COMPANY
Chennai	B-LOCATION

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Data	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
Information	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
@	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Bombay,	I-INSTITUTION
Mumbai,	B-LOCATION
completed	O
2008-2011,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
9.1	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Organisation	O
:	O
Tata	B-COMPANY
Elxsi	I-COMPANY

MBA	B-DEGREE
Systems,	B-FIELD
Osmania	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
(part-time),	O
64%	B-GRADE

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(IT)	B-FIELD
–	O
JNTU	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
74.8%	B-GRADE

Jul	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Cognizant	B-COMPANY
Technology	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Enterprise	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
–	O
XLRI	B-INSTITUTION
Jamshedpur	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2014-2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
8.5	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Adobe,	B-COMPANY
San	B-LOCATION
Jose,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION

Year	O
:	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END

B.E.:	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
@	O
Pune	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2010–2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
62%	B-GRADE

Sep	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

M.Tech,	B-DEGREE
Pune	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
2016,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
78.3%	B-GRADE

Lead	B-ROLE
SCADA	I-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
Industrial	I-ROLE
IoT	I-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology:	I-DEGREE
IT	B-FIELD
@	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Surathkal	B-LOCATION
|	O
2010–2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
CGPA	O
8.4	B-GRADE

Palo	B-COMPANY
Alto	I-COMPANY
Networks/Santa	B-LOCATION
Clara	I-LOCATION
CA/Staff	B-ROLE
Security	I-ROLE
Engineer/April	B-DATE_START
2023/Present	B-DATE_END

Associate	B-ROLE
Director	I-ROLE
–	I-ROLE
Technology	I-ROLE
|	O
Vantage	B-COMPANY
Biotech	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY
|	O
2017	B-DATE_START
–	O
2021	B-DATE_END

Systems	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Snowflake#Boston	B-LOCATION
MA#Data	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
III#Oct2021#Present#client:Capital	B-CLIENT
One	I-CLIENT

Intern	B-ROLE
@	O
Syntel	B-COMPANY
|	O
Pune	B-LOCATION
|	O
Jan	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
-	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

Company	O
:	O
Lyft	B-COMPANY

Wipro,	B-COMPANY
Delhi	B-LOCATION

Jun	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Mechanical)	B-FIELD
–	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Trichy	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
8.4	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

CGPA:	O
7.6	B-GRADE

Google	B-COMPANY
•	O
Mountain	B-LOCATION
View,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION

Jun	B-DATE_START
2009	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Engineering:Civil::JNTU::Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
India::2009::2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Cyber	B-FIELD
Security	I-FIELD
–	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2108-2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
9.0	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Lucknow	B-LOCATION

2016	B-DATE_START
–	O
2020	B-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE

Senior	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

B.Tech:	B-DEGREE
CSE	B-FIELD
@	O
JNTU	B-COMPANY
Anantapur	B-LOCATION
|	O
2011–2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
72.4%	B-GRADE

Apr	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Role	O
:	O
Web	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Software	B-ROLE
Developer,	I-ROLE
Chennai,	B-LOCATION
2018	B-DATE_START
-	O
2021	B-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Patna	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
79%	B-GRADE

Patni	B-COMPANY
Computer	I-COMPANY
Systems	I-COMPANY

Master	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science:	I-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Information	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
–	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Surathkal	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2014-2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
8.0	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology,	I-DEGREE
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Roorkee,	I-INSTITUTION
Roorkee	I-INSTITUTION
Campus,	I-INSTITUTION
2014-2017,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
8.3	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Embedded	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
–	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Roorkee	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2017-2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
8.6	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Position:	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
–	O
Payments	O

Jun	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END

iGate!!Bangalore	B-LOCATION
India!!Software	B-ROLE
Developer!!September	B-DATE_START
2013!!June	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
(CS)	B-FIELD
BITS	B-INSTITUTION
Pilani	I-INSTITUTION
Pilani	I-INSTITUTION
Campus	I-INSTITUTION
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
8.5	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Sr.	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
SAP	B-COMPANY
Labs	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore,	B-LOCATION
Karnataka	I-LOCATION
|	O
2020	B-DATE_START
-	O
Present	B-DATE_END

TCS	B-COMPANY
~	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
~	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
~	O
2016–2019	B-DATE_END

Associate	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Software	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
@	O
TCS	B-COMPANY
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
|	O
03/2017	B-DATE_START
-	O
05/2019	B-DATE_END

Wipro,	B-COMPANY
Chennai	B-LOCATION

2018–2020	B-DATE_END

Palantir	B-COMPANY
Technologies;Denver	B-LOCATION
CO;Principal	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Architect;April	B-DATE_START
2022;Present	B-DATE_END

October	O
–	O
May201	O
Graphics	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Genpact	B-COMPANY
India,	B-LOCATION
Gurugram	I-LOCATION

Duration	O
:	O
March	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Till	B-DATE_END
Date	I-DATE_END

Jul	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

Client:	O
ABB	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT

Jun	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

2016	B-DATE_START
–	O
2020	B-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Joined	O
Infosys	B-COMPANY
(Mumbai)	B-LOCATION
as	O
Sr	B-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
in	O
Jan	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
–	O
Client:	O
WHO	B-CLIENT
Regulatory	I-CLIENT

Process	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
cum	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Jaipur	B-LOCATION

Jul	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

SAP	B-COMPANY
|	O
Newtown	B-LOCATION
Square,	I-LOCATION
PA	I-LOCATION

Nutanix	B-COMPANY
|	O
San	B-LOCATION
Jose	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
|	O
Distinguished	B-ROLE
Cloud	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
|	O
September	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
|	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE

Trainee	B-ROLE

Cyient	B-COMPANY
::	O
Embedded	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
::	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
::	O
Mar'19	B-DATE_START
to	O
Aug'21	B-DATE_END

Pursued	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Engineering:	I-DEGREE
Information	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
and	O
graduated	O
in	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
from	O
VIT	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
Vellore,	B-LOCATION
India.	I-LOCATION

Microsoft	B-COMPANY
(Client:	O
Azure	B-CLIENT
Cognitive	I-CLIENT
Services)	I-CLIENT
|	O
2022	B-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
|	O
Redmond,	B-LOCATION
WA	I-LOCATION
(Hybrid)	O

Jul	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Business	B-FIELD
Analytics	I-FIELD
–	O
IIM	B-INSTITUTION
Ahmedabad	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2015-2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
8.9	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Jan'16	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'18	B-DATE_END

Did	O
my	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
from	O
Georgia	B-INSTITUTION
Tech	I-INSTITUTION
in	O
Aerospace	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
(2013-2015),	B-EDU_YEAR_END
86%	B-GRADE

UST	B-COMPANY
Global,	I-COMPANY
Trivandrum	B-LOCATION

Trainee	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Senior	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Junior	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Jan	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
Jadavpur	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Kolkata	B-LOCATION
–	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
79.2%	B-GRADE

Currently	O
working	O
with	O
TCS	B-COMPANY
as	O
Lead	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
(since	O
March	B-DATE_START
2021)	I-DATE_START
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION

Osmania	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
|	O
Information	B-FEILD
Technology	I-FEILD
|	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
|	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
79.8%	B-GRADE

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology,	I-DEGREE
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Madras,	I-INSTITUTION
Chennai	I-INSTITUTION
Campus,	I-INSTITUTION
2012-2016,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
8.9	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

NIIT	B-COMPANY
Technologies;Delhi	B-LOCATION
India;Software	B-ROLE
Developer;April	B-DATE_START
2015;December	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

Jan	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

2019–2022	B-DATE_END

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology:	I-DEGREE
ECE	B-FIELD
@	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Warangal	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2013–2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
8.6	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Year	O
:	O
2010–2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END

T-Mobile,	B-COMPANY
Bellevue,	B-LOCATION
WA	I-LOCATION

Palantir	B-COMPANY
Technologies;Denver	B-LOCATION
CO;Principal	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Architect;April	B-DATE_START
2022;Present	B-DATE_END

Telecom	B-ROLE
Applications	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
August	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
April	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END

June20	B-DATE_START
–	O
Februar	O
Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Principal	B-ROLE
Site	I-ROLE
Reliability	I-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
Cloud	I-ROLE
Operations	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE

Platform	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END

Pune	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
India	O
·	O
2007–2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Cape	B-LOCATION
Canaveral,	I-LOCATION
FL	I-LOCATION

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
-	O
Lead	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
-	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
(2015	B-DATE_START
-	O
2019)	B-DATE_END

Capgemini,	B-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

Field:	O
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD

B.E.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Gujarat	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Ahmedabad	B-LOCATION
–	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
69.4%	B-GRADE

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
–	O
Network	O
January	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
July	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
CSE,	B-FIELD
JNTU	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad,	B-LOCATION
2011,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
69.8%	B-GRADE

Infosys	B-COMPANY
Ltd,	I-COMPANY
Senior	B-ROLE
Developer,	I-ROLE
Noida,	B-LOCATION
2016	B-DATE_START
-	O
Jan	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END

Security	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Razorpay	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore,	B-LOCATION
Karnataka	I-LOCATION
|	O
February	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Year	O
:	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END

B.E.:	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
@	O
Mumbai	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2010–2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
68.4%	B-GRADE

M.Tech:	B-DEGREE
VLSI	B-FIELD
Design	I-FIELD
@	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Kharagpur	B-LOCATION
|	O
2015–2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Analyst	B-ROLE
/	O
Associate	O

Amazon,	B-COMPANY
Seattle,	B-LOCATION
WA	I-LOCATION
-	O
Sr.	B-ROLE
Cloud	I-ROLE
Solutions	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
(March	B-DATE_START
2022–Present)	B-DATE_END

Hexaware	B-COMPANY
Technologies,Chennai	B-LOCATION
India,Java	B-ROLE
Lead,June	B-DATE_START
2018,December	B-DATE_END
2020,client:SwiftPay	B-CLIENT
FinTech	I-CLIENT

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
Mathematics	B-FIELD
and	I-FIELD
Computing,	I-FIELD
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi,	B-LOCATION
2013,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
CGPA:	O
9.2/10	B-GRADE

DELOITTE	B-COMPANY
|	O
Technology	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
|	O
2022/01	B-DATE_START
–	O
Current	B-DATE_END
|	O
Gurugram	B-LOCATION

Product	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
CRED	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
Mar'21	B-DATE_START
to	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
III	I-ROLE
@	O
Oracle	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
|	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
|	O
January	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
ECE,	B-FIELD
Graphic	B-INSTITUTION
Era	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
Dehradun,	B-LOCATION
2016,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
68.2%	B-GRADE

Senior	B-ROLE
QA	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
Anna	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
78%	B-GRADE

Senior	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
–	O
Software	O

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
@	O
UC	B-INSTITUTION
San	I-INSTITUTION
Diego,	I-INSTITUTION
San	B-LOCATION
Diego,	I-LOCATION
completed	O
2008-2011,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
9.0	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Score:	O
79.8%	B-GRADE

SDE	B-ROLE
@	O
Flipkart	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
03/2017	B-DATE_START
-	O
12/2019	B-DATE_END

Client:	O
Ford	B-CLIENT
Motor	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

2015–2018	B-DATE_END

Persistent	B-COMPANY
Systems,	I-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

ServiceNow	B-COMPANY
|	O
Santa	B-LOCATION
Clara,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Kolkata	B-LOCATION

Infosys	B-COMPANY
~	O
Software	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
~	O
Coimbatore	B-LOCATION
~	O
2018–2021	B-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Trainee	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Solutions	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Junior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Dev	I-ROLE
@	O
WIPRO	B-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
Sep'16	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'18	B-DATE_END

Jun	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology:	I-DEGREE
CSE	B-FIELD
@	O
Kakatiya	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2011–2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
74.8%	B-GRADE

Happiest	B-COMPANY
Minds	I-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

AMAZON	B-COMPANY
INDIA	I-COMPANY
|	O
Site	B-ROLE
Reliability	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
|	O
2020/07	B-DATE_START
–	O
Current	B-DATE_END
|	O
Bengaluru	B-LOCATION

Pure	B-COMPANY
Storage	I-COMPANY
|	O
Mountain	B-LOCATION
View	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
|	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
|	O
March	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
|	O
August	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END

Tech	B-COMPANY
Mahindra	I-COMPANY
::	O
Associate	B-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE
::	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
::	O
Jan'17	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'18	B-DATE_END

B.E.	B-DEGREE
Electrical	B-FIELD
&	I-FIELD
Electronics,	I-FIELD
PSG	B-INSTITUTION
Tech	I-INSTITUTION
Coimbatore,	B-LOCATION
2016,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
78%	B-GRADE

Wipro	B-COMPANY
Limited,	I-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

San	B-LOCATION
Jose,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
/	I-LOCATION
APAC	I-LOCATION

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
@	O
TCS	B-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
July	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
-	O
Feb	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

TechLead|Jun2018|Dec2023	B-DATE_END

Infrastructure	B-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

Location	O
:	O
San	B-LOCATION
Francisco,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION

Junior	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology,	I-DEGREE
IIT	B-LOCATION
Hyderabad,	I-LOCATION
Hyderabad	I-LOCATION
Campus,	I-LOCATION
2013-2017,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
8.8	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Senior	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Trainee	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Amazon	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
|	O
DevOps	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
|	O
Bengaluru	B-LOCATION
|	O
May'20	B-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
|	O
Client:	O
Flipkart	B-CLIENT

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Distributed	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
–	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2017-2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
9.2	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

SeniorManager::Feb2019::Mar2024	B-DATE_END

Client:	O
Schlumberger	B-CLIENT

Technical	B-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE

Institution:	O
Manipal	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
India	B-LOCATION

Title	O
:	O
API	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Client:	O
Syntel	B-CLIENT
|	O
Java	O
development	O
for	O
US	O
financial	O
client	O

Jul	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

Nashville,	B-LOCATION
TN	I-LOCATION
/	I-LOCATION
National	I-LOCATION

B.Tech:Electronics	B-FIELD
and	I-FIELD
Instrumentation,NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Warangal,Telangana	B-LOCATION
India(2008-2012)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Period:	O
September	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END

[2022	B-DATE_START
–	O
Present]	B-DATE_END
Sr.	B-ROLE
Video	I-ROLE
Platform	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
→	O
Zoom,	B-COMPANY
San	B-LOCATION
Jose,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION

B.Tech:	B-DEGREE
Information	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
@	O
RVCE	B-INSTITUTION
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
2011–2015	B-DATE_END
|	O
74.1%	B-GRADE

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Noida	B-LOCATION

Cognizant	B-COMPANY
Technology	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY
~	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
~	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
~	O
2014–2017	B-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
|	O
Aug	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
-	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
VTU	B-INSTITUTION
Belgaum	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Belgaum	B-LOCATION
–	O
2006-2009	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
71%	B-GRADE

Project	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

Jan	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

iGate|Bangalore	B-LOCATION
India|Software	B-ROLE
Developer|September	B-DATE_START
2014|March	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE
@	O
Infosys	B-COMPANY
|	O
Mysore	B-LOCATION
|	O
Aug	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
-	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

Jan	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

B.E.,	B-DEGREE
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Mumbai,	I-INSTITUTION
2014,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
70%	B-GRADE

2017	B-DATE_START
to	O
2019	B-DATE_END

Mphasis	B-COMPANY
/	O
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
/	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
/	O
2015	B-DATE_START
-	O
2018	B-DATE_END

Integration	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
July	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END

Oklahoma	B-LOCATION
City,	I-LOCATION
OK	I-LOCATION

Completed	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Technology:	I-DEGREE
Electronics	B-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
Communication	I-ROLE
from	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Trichy,	I-INSTITUTION
India	O
in	O
2011.	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Trainee	B-ROLE
@	O
Wipro	B-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
2013	B-DATE_START
-	O
2014	B-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE
@	O
TATA	B-COMPANY
Elxsi	I-COMPANY
|	O
Trivandrum	B-LOCATION
|	O
Aug	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
-	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

>>	O
Anna	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION

Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Wipro	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bengaluru	B-LOCATION
|	O
January	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Senior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Qualification:	O
Master	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science:	I-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD

Senior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Kolkata	B-LOCATION

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Jun	B-DATE_START
2008	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2009	I-DATE_END

Hexaware	B-COMPANY
Technologies~Chennai	B-LOCATION
India~Software	B-ROLE
Developer~March	B-DATE_START
2015~July	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END

Trainee	B-ROLE
@	O
NIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Technologies	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
Delhi	B-LOCATION
|	O
2014	B-DATE_START
-	O
2015	B-DATE_END

Arlington,	B-LOCATION
VA	I-LOCATION

First	O
Class	O
–	O
80.6%	B-GRADE

GOOGLE	B-COMPANY
INDIA	I-COMPANY
|	O
Staff	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
|	O
2021/11	B-DATE_START
–	O
Current	B-DATE_END
|	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Cognizant,	B-COMPANY
Chennai	B-LOCATION

Jul	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
II	I-ROLE
-	O
Snapchat,	B-COMPANY
Santa	B-LOCATION
Monica,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
(November	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
-	O
June	B-DATE_END
2022)	I-DATE_END

PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
in	O
Data	B-FIELD
Science,	I-FIELD
CDAC	B-INSTITUTION
Pune	B-LOCATION
(part-time,	O
pursuing)	O

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
II	I-ROLE
@	O
Flipkart	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore,	B-LOCATION
Karnataka	I-LOCATION
|	O
Jan'21	B-DATE_START
to	O
Dec'22	B-DATE_END

Intern	B-ROLE
@	O
Wipro	B-COMPANY
|	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
|	O
Jul	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
-	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

Jan	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

Jan	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
VIT	B-INSTITUTION
Vellore	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
82%	B-GRADE

Engineer	B-ROLE
@	O
Infosys	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
|	O
Mysore	B-LOCATION
|	O
2015	B-DATE_START
-	O
2018	B-DATE_END

Cognizant	B-COMPANY
Technology	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY

Jan	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Employer:	O
Stripe	B-COMPANY

Bangalore	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
|	O
Computer	B-FIELD
Networks	I-FIELD
|	O
Bengaluru	B-LOCATION
|	O
2009-2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
77.9%	B-GRADE

Duration	O
:	O
March	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
July	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END

L&T	B-COMPANY
Infotech	I-COMPANY
~	O
Tech	B-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE
~	O
Trivandrum	B-LOCATION
~	O
Jan'17	B-DATE_START
to	O
Jan'20	B-DATE_END

JNTU	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
|	O
Artificial	B-FIELD
Intelligence	I-FIELD
|	O
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION
|	O
2012-2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
84.7%	B-GRADE

Cognizant	B-COMPANY
Technology	I-COMPANY
Solutions,	I-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

Client:	O
T-Mobile	B-CLIENT
USA	I-CLIENT
|	O
Billing	O
system	O
development	O
in	O
Java/Oracle	O

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
CSE,	B-FIELD
Pune	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
2016,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
CGPA:	O
7.8/10	B-GRADE

Year	O
:	O
2006–2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END

B.E.	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science,	I-FIELD
Anna	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
Chennai,	B-LOCATION
2018,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
74.2%	B-GRADE

University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Texas,	I-INSTITUTION
Austin	B-LOCATION
(2012–2014)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Wipro,Bangalore	B-LOCATION
India,Senior	B-ROLE
Developer,April	B-DATE_START
2017-May	B-DATE_END
2020,client:FinCore	B-CLIENT
Technologies	I-CLIENT

MBA:	B-DEGREE
Information	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
@	O
Symbiosis	B-INSTITUTION
Pune	B-LOCATION
|	O
2014–2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Citibank	B-COMPANY
(Software	B-ROLE
Developer)	I-ROLE
Tampa,	B-LOCATION
FL	I-LOCATION
June	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
to	O
February	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

B.Tech:	B-DEGREE
CSE	B-FIELD
@	O
JNTU	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2007–2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
|	O
79%	B-GRADE

Employer:	O
American	B-COMPANY
Express	I-COMPANY

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY

Director	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
Energy	I-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
Utilities	I-ROLE
IT	I-ROLE
|	O
GridForce	B-COMPANY
Energy	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY
|	O
2020	B-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Wipro,	B-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
@	O
UC	B-INSTITUTION
Berkeley,	I-INSTITUTION
Berkeley,	B-LOCATION
completed	O
2006-2009,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
9.4	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Intern	B-ROLE
@	O
HCL	B-COMPANY
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
|	O
Apr	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
-	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
JNTU	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
74%	B-GRADE

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Gurugram	B-LOCATION

2013	B-DATE_START
–	O
2016	B-DATE_END

M.Tech:	B-DEGREE
Financial	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
@	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Bombay	B-LOCATION
|	O
2013–2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Mphasis	B-COMPANY
Ltd.	I-COMPANY

Jan	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END

Institution:	O
George	B-INSTITUTION
Mason	I-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
Fairfax,	B-LOCATION
VA	I-LOCATION

QA	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Tech	B-COMPANY
Mahindra	I-COMPANY
|	O
Hyd	B-LOCATION
|	O
2016	B-DATE_START
-	O
2019	B-DATE_END

Year	O
:	O
2012	O

Google,	B-COMPANY
Mountain	B-LOCATION
View,	I-LOCATION
CA	O
-	O
Principal	B-ROLE
Cloud	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
(June	B-DATE_START
2021–Present)	B-DATE_END

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
CSE,	B-FIELD
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Calicut,	I-INSTITUTION
2014,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
74%	B-GRADE

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
Computer	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
@	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Washington,	I-INSTITUTION
Seattle,	B-LOCATION
completed	O
2009-2012,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
9.5	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

Infosys	B-COMPANY
Ltd,	I-COMPANY
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer,	I-ROLE
Noida,	B-LOCATION
2017	B-DATE_START
-	O
2020	B-DATE_END

Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
IT,	B-FIELD
SRM	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Science	I-INSTITUTION
and	I-INSTITUTION
Technology,	I-INSTITUTION
2018,	B-EDU_YEAR_END
CGPA:	O
8.4	B-GRADE

Sr.	B-ROLE
DevOps	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Zepto	B-COMPANY
|	O
Mumbai	B-LOCATION
|	O
Feb	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
-	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Accenture	B-COMPANY
::	O
Senior	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
::	O
Bangalore	B-LOCATION
::	O
2016–2020	B-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
II	I-ROLE
@	O
Twitter	B-COMPANY
|	O
San	B-LOCATION
Francisco,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
|	O
September	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
-	O
March	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END

ACCENTURE	B-COMPANY
|	O
Cloud	B-ROLE
Solutions	I-ROLE
Lead	I-ROLE
|	O
2019/08	B-DATE_START
–	O
Current	B-DATE_END
|	O
Mumbai	B-LOCATION

Minnetonka,	B-LOCATION
MN	I-LOCATION
|	O
February	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
|	O
Full-time	O

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
Mumbai	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
Mumbai	B-LOCATION
–	O
2007-2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
73%	B-GRADE

M.Tech	B-DEGREE
Information	B-FIELD
Security	I-FIELD
–	O
Anna	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
8.1	B-GRADE
CGPA	O

CGPA:	O
8.7	B-GRADE

NIIT	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Hyderabad	B-LOCATION

Software	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Oct	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

Zensar	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Pune	B-LOCATION

College:	O
Mumbai	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION

Intel-Santa	B-LOCATION
Clara,CA-Cloud	B-ROLE
Infrastructure	I-ROLE
Engineer-February	B-DATE_START
2017-July	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END

Organisation	O
:	O
SAIC	B-COMPANY

2017	B-DATE_START
-	O
2020	B-DATE_END

Infosys,	B-COMPANY
Kolkata	B-LOCATION

ProjectLead@Aug2019@Apr2024	B-DATE_END

College	O
:	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Patna	I-INSTITUTION

Jun	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END

Publicis	B-COMPANY
Sapient~Gurgaon	B-LOCATION
India~Senior	B-ROLE
Associate~October	B-DATE_START
2018~February	B-DATE_END
2021~client~TrustArc	B-CLIENT
Insurance	I-CLIENT

Jun	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END

DevOps	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
June	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

[2019	B-DATE_START
–	O
2022]	B-DATE_END
Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
II	I-ROLE
→	O
Slack	B-COMPANY
(Salesforce),	O
San	B-LOCATION
Francisco,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION

B.Tech	B-DEGREE
–	O
Delhi	B-INSTITUTION
Technological	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
–	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
–	O
76%	B-GRADE

Software	B-COMPANY
Developer	I-COMPANY

Robinhood|Menlo	B-LOCATION
Park	I-LOCATION
CA|Staff	B-ROLE
Platform	I-ROLE
Engineer|October	B-DATE_START
2021|Present	B-DATE_END

HCL	B-COMPANY
Technologies,	I-COMPANY
Nagpur	B-LOCATION

Wipro,	B-COMPANY
Bangalore	B-LOCATION

Gujarat	B-INSTITUTION
University,	I-INSTITUTION
India	B-LOCATION

Cloudflare	B-COMPANY
•	O
San	B-LOCATION
Francisco,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION

Software	B-COMPANY
Engineer	I-COMPANY

M.Tech:Artificial	B-FIELD
Intelligence,IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad,Telangana	I-INSTITUTION
India(2014-2016)	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Backend	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
-	O
Pinterest,	B-COMPANY
San	B-LOCATION
Francisco,	I-LOCATION
CA	I-LOCATION
(April	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
-	O
October	B-DATE_END
2019)	I-DATE_END

B.Tech:	B-DEGREE
CSE	B-FIELD
@	O
SRM	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
Chennai	I-INSTITUTION
|	O
2009–2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Did	O
my	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
from	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Texas	I-INSTITUTION
at	O
Austin	B-LOCATION
in	O
Network	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
(2010-2012),	B-EDU_YEAR_START
83%	B-GRADE

Jadavpur	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
>>	O
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
>>	O
2012-2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
>>	O
82.6%	B-GRADE

Percentage:	O
75.8%	B-GRADE

Publicis	B-COMPANY
Sapient,	I-COMPANY
Gurugram	B-LOCATION

Systems	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END

2016–2019	B-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

Wipro	B-COMPANY
::	O
Security	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
::	O
Coimbatore	B-LOCATION
::	O
Aug'18	B-DATE_START
to	O
Mar'20	B-DATE_END

Software	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
@	O
Zoho	B-COMPANY
|	O
Chennai	B-LOCATION
|	O
03/2016	B-DATE_START
-	O
12/2018	B-DATE_END

Apr	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END

Cognizant,	B-COMPANY
Kolkata	B-LOCATION

TCS,	B-COMPANY
Mumbai	B-LOCATION

Jul	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END

VP	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
Engineering	I-ROLE
|	O
Stellar	B-COMPANY
Systems	I-COMPANY
Inc	I-COMPANY
|	O
2017	B-DATE_START
–	O
2021	B-DATE_END

Client:	O
Hindustan	B-CLIENT
Unilever	I-CLIENT

hyderabad,	B-LOCATION
india	I-LOCATION
·	O
august	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
may	B-DEGREE
2014	I-DEGREE

Junior	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE

