[
  {
    "tokens": [
      "HR",
      "Analyst",
      "Mphasis",
      "Bangalore",
      "(2019",
      "to",
      "2021)",
      "client",
      "NA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "EPAM",
      "India,",
      "Pune"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dec",
      "2019",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Principal",
      "Payments",
      "Architecture",
      "&",
      "PCI",
      "Compliance",
      "Lead"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "(Industries",
      "Group",
      "A.G.,",
      "client",
      ":",
      "Enterprises",
      "Technologies",
      "International,",
      "Digital",
      "Health",
      "Engineer,",
      "Lucknow,",
      "2014–2017)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "II",
      "@",
      "Twitter",
      "|",
      "San",
      "Francisco,",
      "CA",
      "|",
      "September",
      "2017",
      "-",
      "March",
      "2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Data",
      "Analyst"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Cognizant",
      "Technology",
      "Solutions,",
      "Pune"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apr",
      "2021",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Designation",
      ":",
      "Senior",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Master",
      "of",
      "Engineering:Robotics;University",
      "of",
      "Michigan;Ann",
      "Arbor",
      "MI;2015;2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Completed",
      "M.Sc",
      "Pharmacology",
      "from",
      "Manipal",
      "University",
      "(2005-2007)",
      "with",
      "8.4",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Standard",
      "Chartered",
      "Bank"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Year:",
      "2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "mtech",
      "cyber",
      "security",
      "from",
      "IIIT",
      "hyderabad",
      "2012-2014",
      "cgpa",
      "8.1/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "DevOps",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Jio",
      "Platforms",
      "|",
      "Mumbai",
      "|",
      "February",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "2015",
      "–",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "Software",
      "Systems,",
      "BITS",
      "Pilani,",
      "2016",
      "(part-time)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Location",
      ":",
      "Pune,",
      "Maharashtra"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Systems",
      "Administrator",
      "March",
      "2014",
      "–",
      "October",
      "2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "University",
      ":",
      "IISc",
      "Bengaluru"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology:IT,SRM",
      "Institute",
      "of",
      "Science",
      "and",
      "Technology,Chennai",
      "India(2011-2015)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "\\\\",
      "VLSI",
      "Design",
      "\\\\",
      "Mysore",
      "University",
      "\\\\",
      "2010-2012",
      "\\\\",
      "81.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jun",
      "2012",
      "–",
      "Dec",
      "2012"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jul",
      "2020",
      "–",
      "Till",
      "Date",
      "|",
      "Lead",
      "Data",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "HCL",
      "Technologies",
      "|",
      "Hyderabad"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "btech",
      "ece",
      "from",
      "college",
      "of",
      "engineering",
      "guindy",
      "2004-2007",
      "percentage:76.9%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Centene",
      "Corporation",
      "(Client:",
      "WellCare",
      "Health",
      "Plans)",
      "|",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present",
      "|",
      "St.",
      "Louis,",
      "MO",
      "(Remote)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sr.",
      "DevOps",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Zepto",
      "|",
      "Mumbai",
      "|",
      "Feb",
      "2022",
      "-",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Senior",
      "Consultant"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "msc",
      "data",
      "science",
      "from",
      "symbiosis",
      "pune",
      "2012-2014",
      "cgpa",
      "8.6/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Burbank,",
      "CA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Degree:",
      "B.Tech",
      "IT",
      "|",
      "Delhi",
      "Technological",
      "Univ",
      "|",
      "2010–2014",
      "|",
      "76%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "BITS",
      "Pilani",
      "|",
      "2012-2014",
      "|",
      "87.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Spatial",
      "Analyst",
      "MapmyIndia",
      "Delhi",
      "2020",
      "to",
      "2022",
      "client",
      "govt"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mtech",
      "|",
      "Distributed",
      "Systems",
      "|",
      "IIT",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "2013-2015",
      "|",
      "93.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Siemens",
      "Technology",
      "India",
      "-->",
      "Senior",
      "R&D",
      "Engineer",
      "-->",
      "Bangalore",
      "-->",
      "Aug",
      "2021",
      "-",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Schlumberger"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Associate",
      "@",
      "Wipro",
      "Ltd.",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "08/2013",
      "-",
      "06/2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Senior",
      "Associate",
      "–",
      "Data",
      "Engineering"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Senior",
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Mindtree",
      "|",
      "Bengaluru",
      "|",
      "From",
      "2018",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Company",
      ":",
      "Infoysis"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech:Artificial",
      "Intelligence,IIT",
      "Hyderabad,Telangana",
      "India(2014-2016)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apr",
      "2020",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Savitribai",
      "Phule",
      "Pune",
      "University"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "~",
      "Electronics",
      "&",
      "Communication",
      "~",
      "2010-2013",
      "~",
      "Uttarakhand",
      "Technical",
      "University",
      "~",
      "Dehradun",
      "~",
      "8.4",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Embedded",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Texas",
      "Instruments",
      "India",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "January",
      "2021",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech,",
      "Computer",
      "Science,",
      "IIT",
      "Bombay,",
      "2009-2013,",
      "Grade:",
      "A+",
      "(88.4%)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Developer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Apple"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Infoysys",
      "BPO"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Cognizant,",
      "Hyderabad"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Hero",
      "MotoCorp"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jan",
      "2021",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "SAP",
      "SE",
      "Germany"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys",
      "===",
      "Junior",
      "Python",
      "Developer",
      "===",
      "Mumbai",
      "===",
      "2012–2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Score",
      ":",
      "88.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "NIT",
      "Trichy"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Four-plus",
      "years",
      "of",
      "experience",
      "as",
      "Technical",
      "Lead",
      "at",
      "HCL",
      "Technologies,",
      "Bangalore",
      "(2014–2018)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E",
      "–",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "Graduated:",
      "2008-2011",
      "|",
      "76.6%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client",
      "//",
      "ING",
      "Bank",
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E:Electronics",
      "and",
      "Communication;SRM",
      "University;Chennai",
      "India;2008;2012;CGPA6.7/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Osmania",
      "University",
      "College",
      "of",
      "Engineering",
      "|",
      "B.E.",
      "EEE",
      "|",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "2011–2015",
      "|",
      "77%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "mphasis",
      "hr",
      "analyst",
      "jul2016",
      "jun2022",
      "dept:talent",
      "acquisition"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "PGDM",
      "[XLRI",
      "Jamshedpur]",
      "2013",
      "→",
      "8.1",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Associate",
      "Developer",
      "@",
      "Infosys",
      "Technologies",
      "|",
      "Hyd",
      "|",
      "Jan'19",
      "to",
      "Jan'22"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Position",
      "Identity",
      "&",
      "Access",
      "Management",
      "Engineer",
      "Company",
      "Fusion",
      "Hospitality",
      "Company",
      "Client",
      "Smart",
      "Ultra",
      "Corporation",
      "Pune",
      "Sep",
      "2021-Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Previously",
      "served",
      "as",
      "Drug",
      "Safety",
      "Associate",
      "at",
      "UCB",
      "Pharma,",
      "Hyderabad",
      "between",
      "2018",
      "and",
      "2021."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "TCS",
      ">>",
      "Banglore",
      ">>",
      "Jan",
      "2019",
      "to",
      "Till",
      "Date"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Edgewell",
      "Personal",
      "Care",
      "→",
      "Assistant",
      "Brand",
      "Manager",
      "→",
      "Shelton,",
      "CT",
      "→",
      "Aug",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "May",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Intern",
      "@",
      "Summit",
      "Food",
      "Pvt",
      "Ltd",
      "::",
      "Position=Junior",
      "Data",
      "Governance",
      "Engineer",
      "::",
      "Client=None",
      "::",
      "Chennai",
      "::",
      "Apr",
      "2020",
      "-",
      "Jun",
      "2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Institution:",
      "George",
      "Mason",
      "University,",
      "Fairfax,",
      "VA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Accenture",
      "India",
      "|",
      "Enterprise",
      "Architect",
      "|",
      "Bengaluru",
      "|",
      "Apr'18",
      "–",
      "Present",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "BPCL"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Wipro,",
      "Delhi"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech~Computer",
      "Science~Visvesvaraya",
      "Technological",
      "University~2013-2017~8.0/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "YEAR",
      ":",
      "2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jun",
      "2014",
      "–",
      "May",
      "2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Percentage",
      ":",
      "81.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Intern",
      "@",
      "Services",
      "Strategic",
      "Co.",
      "::",
      "Position=Junior",
      "Zero",
      "Trust",
      "Architect",
      "::",
      "Client=None",
      "::",
      "Hyderabad",
      "::",
      "Jul",
      "2022",
      "-",
      "Sep",
      "2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "March",
      "2022",
      "-",
      "Current"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Completed",
      "B.Tech",
      "in",
      "ECE",
      "from",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "in",
      "2016",
      "with",
      "78.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Dev",
      "@",
      "Persistent",
      "Systems",
      "|",
      "Pune",
      "|",
      "Jan'19",
      "to",
      "Dec'22"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Institution:",
      "IIT",
      "Madras,",
      "India"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Duration",
      ":",
      "August",
      "2012",
      "–",
      "September",
      "2014"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "hadoop",
      "developer@Kellton",
      "Tech@Hyderabad@2018@present@client:BPCL"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Accenture",
      "India,",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jan",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "Jun",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "SAIC",
      "-",
      "Cybersecurity",
      "Engineer",
      "-",
      "San",
      "Diego,",
      "CA",
      "-",
      "02/2019",
      "to",
      "06/2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Cognizant",
      "===",
      "Junior",
      "Java",
      "Developer",
      "===",
      "Chennai",
      "===",
      "2014–2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jan",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "May",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "MTech",
      "Space",
      "Tech-IISc-Bangalore-2010-2012-cgpa:9.5/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mu",
      "Sigma",
      "++",
      "Jr",
      "Data",
      "Analyst",
      "++",
      "Bangalore",
      "++",
      "2012–2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Com",
      "Machine",
      "Learning",
      "-",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "-",
      "2012/2016",
      "-",
      "8.2",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Delhi,",
      "Delhi"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "BS",
      "Information",
      "Systems",
      "-",
      "Virginia",
      "Tech",
      "-",
      "2013",
      "to",
      "2017",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.5"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "DEGREE",
      ">",
      "B.Tech",
      "Mining",
      "Engineering"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Capgemini",
      "India,",
      "Noida"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Raymond",
      "James",
      "Financial",
      "Petersburg,",
      "FL"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "→",
      "Mphasis"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Year",
      ":",
      "2006–2010"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Qualcomm",
      "India",
      "|",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "January",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "HEWLETT",
      "PACKARD",
      "ENTERPRISE",
      "|",
      "Infrastructure",
      "Architect",
      "|",
      "2017/04",
      "–",
      "2021/01",
      "|",
      "Chandigarh"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "M.Tech,",
      "AI",
      "&",
      "ML",
      "|",
      "2016-2018",
      "|",
      "8.9"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Score",
      ":",
      "90.5%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "|",
      "Mechanical",
      "&",
      "CS",
      "(Dual)",
      "|",
      "IIT",
      "Guwahati",
      "|",
      "2013–2017",
      "|",
      "CPI:",
      "8.9"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "When",
      ":",
      "Jul",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "Dec",
      "2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "New",
      "York,",
      "NY",
      "/",
      "Europe"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Location:",
      "Trivandrum"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Intern",
      "@",
      "TCS",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "May",
      "2018",
      "-",
      "Nov",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tata",
      "Consultancy",
      "Services",
      "++",
      "Jr",
      "React",
      "Developer",
      "++",
      "Hyderabad",
      "++",
      "2014–2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Completed",
      "B.Tech",
      "in",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "from",
      "CUSAT",
      "in",
      "2015",
      "with",
      "82.6%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Senior",
      "AWS",
      "Developer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.:",
      "CSE",
      "@",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2011-2015",
      "|",
      "69.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "UNIVERSITY",
      ":",
      "BITS",
      "Pilani",
      "(WILP)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Principal",
      "Consultant"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "DELOITTE",
      "|",
      "Technology",
      "Consultant",
      "|",
      "2022/01",
      "–",
      "Current",
      "|",
      "Gurugram"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jan",
      "2019",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "networkEngineer@cisco@Pune@2018@present@client:airtel"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Arlington,",
      "VA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "CITY",
      ":",
      "Mumbai"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology,",
      "IIT",
      "Kharagpur,",
      "Kharagpur",
      "Campus,",
      "2012-2015,",
      "8.2",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "\\\\",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "\\\\",
      "NIT",
      "Patna",
      "\\\\",
      "2015-2019",
      "\\\\",
      "74.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Moogambigai",
      "InfoTech",
      "//",
      "Junior",
      "Developer",
      "//",
      "Chennai",
      "//",
      "2017",
      "Jul",
      "-",
      "2019",
      "Apr"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "iOS",
      "Dev",
      "~",
      "Khatabook",
      "~",
      "client:SME",
      "Merchants",
      "~",
      "Bangalore",
      "~",
      "2021~present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Backend",
      "Eng",
      "+++",
      "Cashfree",
      "Payments",
      "+++",
      "client:Payment",
      "Gateway",
      "+++",
      "Bangalore",
      "+++",
      "Sept2022",
      "+++",
      "running"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "blockchain",
      "developer",
      "|",
      "tcs",
      "|",
      "hyderabad",
      "|",
      "2019",
      "|",
      "present",
      "|",
      "client:sbi"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "MBA",
      "Commodity@NCDEX",
      "Institute@Mumbai@2011@2013@cgpa:7.7/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Software",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "SCORE",
      ":",
      "80.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys,",
      "Bengaluru"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "TCS",
      "|",
      "DevOps",
      "Architect",
      "|",
      "2020/11",
      "–",
      "Current",
      "|",
      "Chennai"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "MBA",
      "(2014–2016)",
      "NMIMS",
      "Mumbai",
      "CGPA",
      "7.4/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "When",
      ":",
      "Mar",
      "2020",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Ropar",
      "|",
      "M.Tech",
      "CS",
      "|",
      "Rupnagar",
      "|",
      "2016–2018",
      "|",
      "8.9/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Meta|Menlo",
      "Park",
      "CA|Staff",
      "Infrastructure",
      "Engineer|September",
      "2020|Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "SAP",
      "Labs",
      "::",
      "Solution",
      "Consultant",
      "::",
      "Bengaluru",
      "::",
      "2018–2021",
      "::",
      "client::Mahindra"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "^^Swiggy^^",
      "^^VP",
      "Engineering^^",
      "^^Bangalore^^",
      "^^Jan2021-Present^^"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Graduated:",
      "2014-2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys,",
      "Chennai"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "L&T",
      "Technology",
      "Services",
      "|",
      "Senior",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "2014–2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Ed",
      "|",
      "Mysore",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2013–2014",
      "|",
      "84%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "devops",
      "consultant",
      "oracle",
      "chennai",
      "2016",
      "present",
      "client",
      "microsoft"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Prestige",
      "Brands",
      "Holdings",
      "→",
      "Marketing",
      "Coordinator",
      "→",
      "Irvington,",
      "NY",
      "→",
      "Jul",
      "2013",
      "–",
      "Jul",
      "2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client",
      ",",
      "Schneider",
      "Electric",
      "France"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "VLSI",
      "Design",
      "–",
      "NIT",
      "Calicut",
      "–",
      "2014–2016",
      "–",
      "80.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Wipro,",
      "Trivandrum"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Wipro",
      "Technologies",
      "|",
      "Hyd",
      "|",
      "Apr'17",
      "to",
      "Dec'20"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Philips",
      "Innovation",
      "Campus,",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "MTech",
      "BigData@JNTU",
      "Kakinada@Kakinada@2010@2012@cgpa:7.7/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Business",
      "Intelligence",
      "Developer:",
      "Oracle",
      "India",
      "|",
      "Location:",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "Tenure:",
      "2019–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Uber",
      "|",
      "New",
      "York",
      "NY",
      "|",
      "Lead",
      "Platform",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "March",
      "2021",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "HCL",
      "Technologies,",
      "Chandigarh"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Trainee",
      "@",
      "Cognizant",
      "|",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "2017",
      "-",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Year",
      ":",
      "2016–2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mphasis"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.",
      "Computer",
      "Science,",
      "PSG",
      "College",
      "of",
      "Technology",
      "Coimbatore,",
      "2018,",
      "CGPA:",
      "8.7"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "HCL",
      "Technologies,",
      "Mumbai"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bancorp",
      "-",
      "Product",
      "Manager",
      "-",
      "Sioux",
      "Falls,",
      "SD",
      "-",
      "06/2018",
      "to",
      "12/2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Airbus"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Palantir",
      "Technologies;Denver",
      "CO;Principal",
      "Software",
      "Architect;April",
      "2022;Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Credit",
      "Agricole"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology:",
      "CSE",
      "@",
      "Kakatiya",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2011–2015",
      "|",
      "74.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "TCS--Mumbai",
      "India--Systems",
      "Engineer--Apr2013--May2017--client:Verizon"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech:",
      "CSE",
      "@",
      "Sathyabama",
      "University",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "2014-2018",
      "|",
      "CGPA:",
      "7.3"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "DevOps",
      "@",
      "TATA",
      "Consultancy",
      "Services",
      "|",
      "Mumbai",
      "|",
      "Jan'19",
      "to",
      "Jan'22"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "no.2",
      "IIIT",
      "Allahabad",
      "|",
      "M.Tech",
      "IT",
      "|",
      "Allahabad",
      "|",
      "2017–2019",
      "|",
      "8.3",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology:",
      "CSE",
      "@",
      "Kakatiya",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2014–2018",
      "|",
      "74.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Bajaj",
      "Auto"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jan",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "May",
      "2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "{title:\"Intern\",",
      "startup:\"Navi",
      "Technologies\",",
      "client:\"Internal",
      "Analytics\",",
      "location:\"Bangalore\",",
      "start:\"Jan",
      "2019\",",
      "end:\"Jun",
      "2019\"}"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Hyderabad"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "ABB",
      "India"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "JOB2:",
      "Unacademy",
      "|",
      "Content",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Bengaluru",
      "|",
      "2017–2020",
      "|",
      "client:",
      "Toppr"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "{title:\"Intern\",",
      "startup:\"Niyo",
      "Solutions\",",
      "client:\"Internal",
      "Fintech\",",
      "location:\"Bangalore\",",
      "start:\"Jul2019\",",
      "end:\"Dec2019\"}"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "BCA",
      "\\\\",
      "Information",
      "Technology",
      "\\\\",
      "IIT",
      "Delhi",
      "\\\\",
      "2003-2005",
      "\\\\",
      "CGPA:",
      "6.23"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "warehouse",
      "lead-DTDC-Bangalore-2012-2014-client:B2BLogistics"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Employer",
      ":",
      "InMobi",
      "Group"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys,",
      "Hyderabad"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Developer",
      "@",
      "Freshworks",
      "|",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "04/2019",
      "-",
      "01/2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Completed",
      "B.E.",
      "Automobile",
      "Engineering",
      "from",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "Chennai",
      "in",
      "2010",
      "scoring",
      "76.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "Electronics",
      "&",
      "Communication,",
      "BHU",
      "Varanasi,",
      "2015,",
      "71.5%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Location",
      ":",
      "Mumbai,",
      "Maharashtra"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Sc",
      "\\\\",
      "Bioinformatics",
      "\\\\",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Hyderabad",
      "\\\\",
      "2014-2016",
      "\\\\",
      "76.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "→",
      "B.Sc",
      "(Computer",
      "Science)",
      "|",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Mumbai",
      "|",
      "2013",
      "|",
      "72.5%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech:Electronics",
      "and",
      "Computer",
      "Engineering,NIT",
      "Trichy,Tamil",
      "Nadu",
      "India(2010-2014)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Siemens;Bangalore",
      "India;Head",
      "of",
      "Development;October",
      "2016;August",
      "2023;client;PowerGrid",
      "Renewables"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "2015–2018",
      "|",
      "Fresenius",
      "Kabi",
      "|",
      "Safety",
      "Officer",
      "|",
      "Pune"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "RPA",
      "Analyst",
      "UIPath",
      "Chennai(2019to2021)client=AxisBank"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Booz",
      "Allen",
      "Hamilton",
      "|",
      "Senior",
      "Consultant",
      "|",
      "McLean,",
      "VA",
      "|",
      "2021–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jan'16",
      "to",
      "Dec'18"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "LOCATION",
      ":",
      "Bengaluru,",
      "Karnataka"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "<",
      "NetApp",
      "India",
      ">",
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "II",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "Apr",
      "2018",
      "-",
      "Sep",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Company",
      ":",
      "Amazon"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "Web",
      "Services",
      "|",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "Jan",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "L&T",
      "Infotech",
      "|",
      "Mumbai",
      "|",
      "03/2016",
      "-",
      "12/2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Sc",
      "–",
      "Information",
      "Technology",
      "Graduated:",
      "2007-2010",
      "|",
      "71.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Exp[1]={firm:\"Zoho",
      "Corp\",",
      "post:\"Product",
      "Architect\",",
      "loc:\"Chennai\",",
      "s:2018,",
      "e:\"Present\",",
      "cli:\"Freshdesk\"}"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Ernst",
      "&",
      "Young",
      "/",
      "Manager",
      "/",
      "Hyderabad",
      "/",
      "Jun",
      "2014",
      "–",
      "Jul",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Cyient",
      "::",
      "Embedded",
      "Engineer",
      "::",
      "Hyderabad",
      "::",
      "Mar'19",
      "to",
      "Aug'21"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Designation",
      ":",
      "Software",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.",
      "–",
      "VTU",
      "Belgaum",
      "–",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "67.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "I",
      "worked",
      "as",
      "Research",
      "Associate",
      "at",
      "Aurobindo",
      "Pharma",
      "in",
      "Hyderabad",
      "from",
      "2019",
      "to",
      "2022."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Associate",
      "Engineer",
      "June",
      "2012",
      "–",
      "February",
      "2014"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "INFOSYS",
      "|",
      "SM",
      "|",
      "Mumbai",
      "|",
      "2019–Present",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "WHO"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mar",
      "2021",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "SCORE",
      ":",
      "72.3%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Stripe~San",
      "Francisco",
      "CA~Software",
      "Engineer",
      "L5~May2017~Jan2021~client:Payments",
      "Core"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "TCS,",
      "Gurugram"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Degree",
      ":",
      "M.Tech"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "broadcast",
      "engineer",
      "Sun",
      "TV",
      "Network",
      "Chennai",
      "2017",
      "2020",
      "client:SunSports"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Engineering:Aerospace~PES",
      "University~Bangalore",
      "India~2011~2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Standard",
      "Life",
      "Aberdeen"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IBM",
      "India",
      "===",
      "Junior",
      "Data",
      "Analyst",
      "===",
      "Pune",
      "===",
      "2013–2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "STREAM",
      ":",
      "Information",
      "Technology"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Intermediate:CEC,Tirumala",
      "Junior",
      "College,Nellore",
      "India(2009-2011)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "UnitedHealth",
      "Group",
      "(Client:",
      "Optum",
      "Rx)",
      "|",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present",
      "|",
      "Eden",
      "Prairie,",
      "MN",
      "(Hybrid)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Graduate",
      "Trainee",
      "@",
      "Wipro",
      "Ltd.",
      "|",
      "Kolkata",
      "|",
      "Jul",
      "2015",
      "-",
      "Jul",
      "2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "/",
      "CSE",
      "/",
      "BITS",
      "Pilani",
      "Goa",
      "/",
      "2015",
      "to",
      "2019",
      "/",
      "8.3",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "HCL",
      "Technologies",
      "(2020–Present)",
      "|",
      "Senior",
      "React",
      "Developer",
      "|",
      "~5",
      "Yrs",
      "|",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Employer:",
      "Dr",
      "Reddys",
      "Labs",
      "|",
      "Designation:",
      "Senior",
      "Scientist",
      "|",
      "Location:",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "Period:",
      "2016–2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Senior",
      "QA",
      "Automation",
      "Lead",
      "&",
      "Performance",
      "Engineering",
      "Manager"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys,",
      "Data",
      "Analyst,",
      "Hyderabad,",
      "March",
      "2017",
      "-",
      "January",
      "2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Master",
      "of",
      "Business",
      "Administration:Technology",
      "Management",
      "~",
      "ISB",
      "Hyderabad",
      "~",
      "India",
      "~",
      "2015",
      "~",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Aug",
      "2014",
      "–",
      "Sep",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Dev",
      "@",
      "Infosys",
      "Technologies",
      "|",
      "Mysore",
      "|",
      "2015",
      "-",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Hyderabad"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Employed",
      "at",
      "Wipro",
      "(Ahmedabad)",
      "as",
      "Senior",
      "Consultant",
      "since",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "MTech:",
      "Information",
      "Technology",
      "@",
      "IIT",
      "Delhi",
      "|",
      "2016–2018",
      "|",
      "CGPA",
