[
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Lucene",
      "Corp",
      "*",
      "Junior",
      "Search",
      "Dev",
      "*",
      "New",
      "York,",
      "NY",
      "*",
      "Mar",
      "2017-Jul",
      "2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "→",
      "Jr",
      "Mobile",
      "Developer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Employer:",
      "Stripe"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Paylocity",
      "|",
      "HR",
      "Technology",
      "Specialist",
      "|",
      "Schaumburg,",
      "IL",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Hyatt",
      "Hotels",
      "|",
      "2015–2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "University:",
      "Sardar",
      "Patel",
      "University"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Hyderabad,",
      "TS"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Syntel",
      "|",
      "Java",
      "development",
      "for",
      "US",
      "financial",
      "client"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Inforeliance",
      "Corp",
      "/",
      "Software",
      "Developer",
      "/",
      "Hyderabad",
      "/",
      "Jun",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "Dec",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Ropar",
      "M.Tech",
      "AI",
      "2017–2019",
      "8.9/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Contently",
      "-",
      "Content",
      "Marketing",
      "Associate",
      "-",
      "New",
      "York,",
      "NY",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "IBM",
      "Corporation",
      "-",
      "Since",
      "08/2013",
      "to",
      "05/2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "@",
      "Arcesium",
      "India",
      "Pvt.",
      "Ltd.",
      "//",
      "Quantitative",
      "Developer",
      "//",
      "Hyderabad",
      "//",
      "Mar",
      "2022",
      "-",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.S.",
      "Statistics",
      "(Harvard",
      "University,",
      "2009-2013,",
      "GPA",
      "3.7)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Accenture*Business",
      "Analyst*Mumbai*Sep2021-Nov2024*Client:Reliance",
      "Jio"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Delhi",
      "BCA",
      "Information",
      "Technology",
      "Pune",
      "2013-2017",
      "7.5",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-GRADE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Senior",
      "Engineer",
      "TCS",
      "Hyderabad",
      "2021–2023",
      "Client",
      "HDFC",
      "Bank"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Degree",
      ">>",
      "M.Tech"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Post",
      "Graduate",
      "Program",
      "in",
      "ML",
      "|",
      "Great",
      "Learning",
      "|",
      "2019–2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "FutureLearn",
      "|",
      "Learning",
      "Product",
      "Manager",
      "|",
      "Milton",
      "Keynes,",
      "MK7",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "BBC",
      "Academy",
      "|",
      "2018–2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Science:Electrical",
      "Engineering,IIT",
      "Madras,Chennai",
      "India(2011-2015)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Accenture",
      "•",
      "Java",
      "Developer",
      "•",
      "Bangalore",
      "•",
      "2018–2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "btech",
      "cse",
      "from",
      "sastra",
      "university",
      "thanjavur",
      "2007-2010",
      "cgpa",
      "7.3/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "MS",
      "Network",
      "Engineering",
      "→",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Texas",
      "at",
      "Austin",
      "→",
      "2011–2013",
      "→",
      "GPA",
      "3.7"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology",
      ">>",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "[2011–2015]",
      "(76%)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "·",
      "Syntel"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Darktrace",
      "-",
      "Cybersecurity",
      "Analyst",
      "-",
      "Cambridge,",
      "CB2",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "BT",
      "Group",
      "-",
      "Since",
      "04/2022",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Co:",
      "GCP",
      "|",
      "Tl:",
      "Junior",
      "Dev",
      "|",
      "Cy:",
      "Sunnyvale",
      "CA",
      "|",
      "Yr:",
      "Feb",
      "2016-Apr",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Accenture",
      "-",
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "-",
      "Bangalore,",
      "India",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "Microsoft",
      "-",
      "Since",
      "06/2020",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "→",
      "Software",
      "Developer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "San",
      "Francisco,",
      "CA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jun",
      "2013",
      "–",
      "May",
      "2014"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "LTI",
      "(Larsen",
      "&",
      "Toubro",
      "Infotech),",
      "Pune"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "/",
      "Electronics",
      "/",
      "Kakatiya",
      "University",
      "Warangal",
      "/",
      "2010–2014",
      "/",
      "70.3%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Architect",
      "@",
      "Wipro",
      "Technologies",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "2016",
      "-",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "BS",
      "Accounting",
      "-",
      "San",
      "Francisco",
      "State",
      "University",
      "-",
      "2012",
      "to",
      "2016",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.5"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_START",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Ixigo",
      "(Le",
      "Travenues",
      "Tech)",
      "~",
      "Gurgaon",
      "~",
      "Senior",
      "Engineer",
      "~",
      "Sep",
      "2018",
      "–",
      "May",
      "2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "→",
      "TCS"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology:",
      "CSE",
      "@",
      "Mumbai",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2013-2017",
      "|",
      "71%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "Systems",
      "Engineering",
      "–",
      "BITS",
      "Pilani",
      "–",
      "2015-2017",
      "–",
      "8.7",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "2013–2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mimecast",
      "→",
      "Cloud",
      "Infrastructure",
      "Engineer",
      "→",
      "Lexington,",
      "MA",
      "/",
      "London,",
      "EC4A",
      "→",
      "Client:",
      "Aviva",
      "→",
      "Mar",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Company.............",
      "Tata",
      "1mg",
      "Technologies"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Qualcomm",
      "India",
      "|",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "January",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "<PGDM",
      "Operations>",
      "<IIM",
      "Lucknow>",
      "<2013>",
      "<8.0",
      "CGPA>"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-GRADE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "BSc",
      "Computer",
      "Networks",
      "-",
      "Sheffield",
      "Hallam",
      "University",
      "-",
      "Graduated",
      "2011",
      "-",
      "2:1",
      "Honours"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech:",
      "CSE",
      "@",
      "JNTU",
      "Anantapur",
      "|",
      "2014–2018",
      "|",
      "72.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "–",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "–",
      "Chennai",
      "–",
      "2005-2008",
      "–",
      "79%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Developer",
      "|",
      "Chicago,",
      "IL",
      "|",
      "Jun",
      "2016–Jul",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Cognex",
      "Corporation",
      "-",
      "Robotics",
      "Engineer",
      "-",
      "Natick,",
      "MA",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "General",
      "Motors",
      "-",
      "08/2016",
      "to",
      "06/2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Qualys",
      "Inc.",
      "→",
      "Jr.",
      "Security",
      "Analyst",
      "→",
      "Foster",
      "City,",
      "CA",
      "→",
      "Client:",
      "Oracle",
      "Corporation",
      "→",
      "Jun",
      "2014",
      "–",
      "Feb",
      "2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Senior",
      "Developer",
      "@",
      "IBM",
      "India",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "06/2018",
      "-",
      "12/2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology:Biotechnology_Amrita",
      "University_Coimbatore",
      "India_2012_2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Duration:",
      "2015–2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "BS",
      "Marketing",
      "→",
      "Georgia",
      "State",
      "University",
      "→",
      "2012–2016",
      "→",
      "GPA",
      "3.5"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "YEAR",
      ":",
      "2011-2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "★",
      "Cyber",
      "★",
      "IIT",
      "Kanpur",
      "★",
      "2013-2015",
      "★",
      "9.2",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Joined",
      "Rippling",
      "Inc.",
      "as",
      "Senior",
      "Implementation",
      "Engineer",
      "in",
      "Nashville,",
      "TN",
      "in",
      "May",
      "2021,",
      "working",
      "with",
      "client",
      "HubSpot",
      "Inc."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "Jan'18",
      "to",
      "Feb'21"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.:",
      "Computer",
      "Engineering",
      "@",
      "Mumbai",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2010–2014",
      "|",
      "68.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jan",
      "2019",
      "–",
      "Till",
      "Date",
      "|",
      "Senior",
      "Developer",
      "|",
      "TCS",
      "|",
      "Mumbai"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Qualification:",
      "B.Pharm",
      "|",
      "University:",
      "Manipal",
      "University",
      "|",
      "Year:",
      "2012",
      "|",
      "Marks:",
      "81.7%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Delhivery",
      "Pvt.",
      "Ltd.",
      "/",
      "SDE",
      "I",
      "/",
      "Gurgaon",
      "/",
      "Aug",
      "2017",
      "–",
      "Aug",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech,",
      "NIT",
      "Surat,",
      "2013-2015,",
      "77.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Azure",
      "Synapse",
      ".",
      "Data",
      "Engineer",
      ".",
      "Redmond",
      "WA",
      ".",
      "Client:",
      "Accenture",
      ".",
      "Apr'19",
      "to",
      "Dec'21"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "2014",
      "–",
      "2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sendoso",
      "|",
      "Gifting",
      "Platform",
      "Analyst",
      "|",
      "San",
      "Francisco,",
      "CA",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Twilio",
      "Inc.",
      "|",
      "May",
      "2018–Dec",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IBM",
      "India",
      "Pvt",
      "Ltd,",
      "Kolkata/Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mphasis~Bangalore",
      "India~Trainee",
      "Engineer~August",
      "2015~September",
      "2018~client~AquaCore",
      "Utilities"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Charles",
      "Schwab"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IISc",
      "Bangalore",
      "MCA",
      "Information",
      "Technology",
      "Pune",
      "2014-2016",
      "8.6",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-GRADE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "At",
      "Infosys",
      "I",
      "worked",
      "as",
      "Senior",
      "Systems",
      "Analyst",
      "from",
      "Apr",
      "2017",
      "to",
      "Feb",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "(3)",
      "Wipro",
      "|",
      "Linux",
      "Admin",
      "|",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "2015–2018",
      "|",
      "client:",
      "IOC"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "VLSI",
      "Design",
      "–",
      "NIT",
      "Calicut",
      "–",
      "2014–2016",
      "–",
      "80.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "2014-2018",
      "|",
      "74.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Ufi",
      "VocTech",
      "Trust",
      "|",
      "Curriculum",
      "Developer",
      "|",
      "Birmingham,",
      "B4",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "City",
      "&",
      "Guilds",
      "|",
      "2012–2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Dev",
      "@",
      "Infosys",
      "|",
      "Pune",
      "|",
      "2016",
      "-",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Developer",
      "@",
      "Freshworks",
      "|",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "04/2019",
      "-",
      "01/2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Developer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Full",
      "Stack",
      "Developer:",
      "Zomato",
      "|",
      "Location:",
      "Gurugram",
      "|",
      "Tenure:",
      "2022–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Sc",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "|",
      "Madras",
      "University",
      "|",
      "Graduated",
      "2018",
      "|",
      "Score:",
      "82%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Designation",
      ":",
      "Software",
      "Architect"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Acko",
      "General",
      "Insurance",
      "Principal",
      "Engineer",
      "Bangalore",
      "Nov",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Previously",
      "worked",
      "as",
      "E-Commerce",
      "Platform",
      "Analyst",
      "at",
      "BigCommerce",
      "in",
      "Austin,",
      "TX",
      "from",
      "2018",
      "to",
      "2021,",
      "supporting",
      "client",
      "PetSmart",
      "Inc."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "EarlySalary",
      "SDE",
      "I",
      "Pune",
      "Jun",
      "2017",
      "–",
      "Oct",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Developer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "–",
      "Software",
      "Systems"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "–",
      "Information",
      "Technology",
      "Graduated:",
      "2010-2014",
      "|",
      "79.1%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech:",
      "CSE",
      "@",
      "Lovely",
      "Professional",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2015–2019",
      "|",
      "CGPA:",
      "7.5"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Dev",
      "@",
      "Infosys",
      "|",
      "Hyd",
      "|",
      "Sep",
      "2015",
      "-",
      "Feb",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Leidos",
      "/",
      "Junior",
      "Dev",
      "|",
      "Reston",
      "VA",
      "|",
      "Jun'17-Mar'20"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Braze",
      "-",
      "Marketing",
      "Technology",
      "Manager",
      "-",
      "New",
      "York,",
      "NY",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "American",
      "Eagle",
      "Outfitters",
      "-",
      "04/2022",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "(Apex",
      "Neo",
      "Enterprises)",
      "(Data",
      "Scientist)",
      "(client:Future",
      "Systems",
      "Incorporated)",
      "(Chennai)",
      "(2016–2019)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Location:",
      "Mumbai"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Core",
      "Defense",
      "International",
      "[2021–Present]",
      "→",
      "Principal",
      "AI",
      "Research",
      "Scientist",
      "→",
      "Delhi"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Graduate",
      "Engineer",
      "Trainee",
      "/",
      "Software",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Marketo",
      "+",
      "Junior",
      "Platform",
      "Dev",
      "+",
      "San",
      "Mateo",
      "CA",
      "+",
      "Apr'16",
      "to",
      "Jul'19"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Currently",
      "working",
      "with",
      "Infosys",
      "as",
      "Senior",
      "Manager",
      "(since",
      "Jan",
      "2022)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "TCS",
      "||",
      "Technology",
      "Lead",
      "||",
      "Chennai",
      "||",
      "2019–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Course",
      ":",
      "M.Tech",
      "Computer",
      "Science"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "MS",
      "Finance",
      "-",
      "Santa",
      "Clara",
      "University",
      "-",
      "2014",
      "to",
      "2016",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.8"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_START",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sr.",
      "Dev",
      "@",
      "DXC",
      "Technology",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "Apr'18",
      "to",
      "Dec'21"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "\\\\",
      "Information",
      "Technology",
      "\\\\",
      "RGPV",
      "\\\\",
      "2016-2020",
      "\\\\",
      "73.6%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mindtree",
      "::",
      "Associate",
      "Engineer",
      "::",
      "Bengaluru",
      "::",
      "2016–2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "(Computer",
      "Science)",
      "–",
      "JNTUK",
      "University",
      "-",
      "Kakinada",
      "–",
      "2016",
      "–",
      "82.6%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "(2009",
      "–",
      "2013)",
      "IIT",
      "Roorkee",
      "80.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_START",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      ">>",
      "UNDERGRAD:",
      "B.S.",
      "CS,",
      "UC",
      "Davis,",
      "2010-2014,",
      "GPA",
      "3.5"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "I",
      "worked",
      "as",
      "Research",
      "Associate",
      "at",
      "Aurobindo",
      "Pharma",
      "in",
      "Hyderabad",
      "from",
      "2019",
      "to",
      "2022."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Madras",
      "Chennai",
      "M.Tech",
      "CS",
      "2016–2018",
      "9.2/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Asana",
      ">>",
      "San",
      "Francisco",
      "CA",
      ">>",
      "Senior",
      "Engineering",
      "Manager",
      ">>",
      "February",
      "2021",
      ">>",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech:",
      "AI",
      "&",
      "ML",
      "@",
      "IIIT",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "2015–2017",
      "|",
      "CGPA:",
      "8.6"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jun",
      "2016",
      "–",
      "Jul",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "<B.E",
      "-Mech-",
      "JNTU",
      "Hyderabad",
      "-",
      "2006-2010",
      "-",
      "68%>"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "company=PhonePe,designation=Backend",
      "Developer,base=Bengaluru,joining=2017,leaving=2020,client=NPCI"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Intermediate:CEC,Narayana",
      "Junior",
      "College,Tirupati",
      "India(2010-2012)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Location",
      ":",
      "New",
      "Delhi"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "<Global",
      "Fusion",
      "Ltd.",
      "-",
      "Junior",
      "Data",
      "Analyst",
      "-",
      "Chennai",
      "-",
      "2016–2019>"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "=EDU=",
      "M.Tech",
      "Supply",
      "Chain",
      "Mgmt",
      "|",
      "IIM",
      "Bangalore",
      "(IIMB)",
      "|",
      "2016–2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "zensar",
      "technologies",
      "devops",
      "engineer",
      "mar2016",
      "to",
      "feb2022",
      "clients",
      "hp",
      "and",
      "dell"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys,",
      "Delhi",
      "NCR"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology:",
      "EEE",
      "@",
      "NIT",
      "Calicut",
      "|",
      "2009–2013",
      "|",
      "CGPA:",
      "7.0"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Score",
      ":",
      "79.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Began",
      "as",
      "HR",
      "Coordinator",
      "at",
      "Paylocity",
      "in",
      "Schaumburg,",
      "IL",
      "from",
      "2013",
      "to",
      "2015,",
      "supporting",
      "client",
      "Hyatt",
      "Hotels",
      "Corporation."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "2014"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Gainsight",
      "-",
      "VP",
      "Customer",
      "Success",
      "Operations",
      "-",
      "San",
      "Francisco,",
      "CA",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "Salesforce.com",
      "-",
      "Since",
      "02/2021",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Wipro,",
      "Delhi"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "LOCATION",
      ">",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "(2)",
      "IIT",
      "Delhi",
      "::",
      "M.Tech",
      "CS",
      "::",
      "2016–2018",
      "::",
      "9.2/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-FIELD",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "role",
      "=",
      "Software",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "TCS,",
      "Kolkata"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Oracle|Austin",
      "TX|Lead",
      "Software",
      "Engineer|Mar2017|Jul2020|client:Ford"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.",
      "Mechanical",
      "|",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2009–2013",
      "|",
      "70.5%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_START",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "EDU:",
      "M.Tech",
      "Software",
      "Engg",
      "|",
      "JNTUH",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "2015–2017",
      "|",
      "82%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Adani",
      "Ports",
      "and",
      "SEZ",
      ":::",
      "Chief",
      "Operations",
      "Officer",
      ":::",
      "Ahmedabad",
      ":::",
      "2020–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "BEng",
      "Software",
      "Engineering",
      "→",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Adelaide",
      "→",
      "Graduated",
      "2013",
      "→",
      "GPA",
      "3.8"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      ":",
      "BASE",
      ":",
      "Gurgaon",
      ":"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "SDE",
      "I",
      "@",
      "Razorpay",
      "|",
      "Bangalore,",
      "Karnataka",
      "|",
      "Feb",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "BSc",
      "Mathematics",
      "and",
      "Statistics",
      "-",
      "Monash",
      "University",
      "-",
      "Graduated",
      "2011",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.7"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "NVIDIA",
      "India",
      ">>",
      "Deep",
      "Learning",
      "Engineer",
      ">>",
      "Pune",
      ">>",
      "Nov",
      "2021",
      "-",
      "Now"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "PGDM",
      "Marketing",
      "–",
      "XLRI",
      "Jamshedpur",
      "–",
      "2015–2017",
      "–",
      "8.4",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "NIIT",
      "Technologies>QA",
      "Engineer>Jaipur>June2016-May2020>Client:BookMyShow"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "2007",
      "–",
      "2010"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Palantir",
      "Technologies",
      "→",
      "Operations",
      "Research",
      "Analyst",
      "→",
      "Washington,",
      "DC",
      "→",
      "Client:",
      "Department",
      "of",
      "Defense",
      "→",
      "Feb",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Immersive",
      "Labs",
      "|",
      "Cyber",
      "Training",
      "Manager",
      "|",
      "Bristol,",
      "BS1",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Zurich",
      "Insurance",
      "UK",
      "|",
      "2016–2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Org:",
      "MakeMyTrip",
      "India",
      "|",
      "Post:",
      "SDE",
      "III",
      "|",
      "Base:",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "Since:",
      "May",
      "2018",
      "till",
      "Dec",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mimecast",
      "India",
      "|",
      "Senior",
      "Security",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Pune",
      "|",
      "Oct",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Trainee",
      "@",
      "Cognizant",
      "|",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "Aug",
      "2018",
      "-",
      "Mar",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "{FIRM}",
      "Latent",
      "View",
      "Analytics"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Principal",
      "Network",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Gurgaon",
      "|",
      "Mar",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Completed",
      "B.Tech",
      "in",
      "ECE",
      "from",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "in",
      "2016",
      "with",
      "78.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "ORG:",
      "Raytheon",
      "BBN",
      "|",
      "POS:",
      "Research",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "LOC:",
      "Cambridge",
      "MA",
      "|",
      "CLI:",
      "DARPA",
      "|",
      "DT:",
      "Apr",
      "2019-Dec",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "{CITY}",
      "Gurgaon"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "MS",
      "Finance",
      "→",
      "University",
      "of",
      "San",
      "Francisco",
      "→",
      "2011–2013",
      "→",
      "GPA",
      "3.6"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "PhD",
      "Computer",
      "Vision",
      "|",
      "IISc",
      "Bengaluru",
      "|",
      "2016–2021",
      "|",
      "Published",
      "4",
      "Papers"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      ">",
      "[2016-2018]",
      "M.Tech",
      "AI",
      "::",
      "IIIT",
      "Delhi",
      "::",
      "8.8",
      "GPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "[2020–Present]",
      "Tata",
      "Motors,",
      "General",
      "Manager",
      "–",
      "Operations,",
      "Pune"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_END",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Started",
      "career",
      "as",
      "Graduate",
      "Developer",
      "at",
      "Nitro",
      "Software,",
      "San",
      "Francisco",
      "CA",
      "/",
      "Sydney",
      "NSW",
      "2000",
      "from",
      "March",
      "2012",
      "to",
      "May",
      "2015,",
      "working",
      "for",
      "client",
      "PwC",
      "Australia."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Currently",
      "employed",
      "as",
      "Director",
      "of",
      "Product",
      "Management",
      "at",
      "Apttus",
      "(Conga),",
      "Broomfield,",
      "CO",
      "since",
      "June",
      "2022,",
      "serving",
      "client",
      "Oracle",
      "Corporation."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "Artificial",
      "Intelligence",
      "|",
      "2018-2020",
      "|",
      "CGPA",
      "8.4"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Raymond",
      "James",
      "Financial",
      "Petersburg,",
      "FL"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mahindra",
      "and",
      "Mahindra",
      "===",
      "Junior",
      "Firmware",
      "Engineer",
      "===",
      "Nashik",
      "===",
      "2012–2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Multiverse",
      "|",
      "Learning",
      "Experience",
      "Designer",
      "|",
      "London,",
      "E1W",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Deloitte",
      "UK",
      "|",
      "2021–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "•",
      "Data",
      "Science",
      "•",
      "IIT",
      "Bombay",
      "•",
      "2013-2015",
      "•",
      "84.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "[Company]:",
      "Solr",
      "|",
      "[Role]:",
      "Search",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "[City]:",
      "Chicago",
      "IL",
      "|",
      "[Client]:",
      "Tribune",
      "|",
      "[Period]:",
      "Sep",
      "2019-Feb",
      "2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apr",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "2016",
      "→",
      "2018",
      "Junior",
      "Developer",
      "Yodlee",
      "Infotech",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "(M.Tech,",
      "Symbiosis",
      "Institute",
      "of",
      "Technology,",
      "Pune,",
      "2017,",
      "76.8%)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "May",
      "2019-Dec",
      "2021",
      "|",
      "Booz",
      "Allen",
      "Hamilton",
      "|",
      "Data",
      "Analyst",
      "|",
      "McLean",
      "VA",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "NSA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.:",
      "CSE",
      "|",
      "2013-2017",
      "|",
      "CGPA",
      "7.5/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Pharma",
      "Solutions",
      "GmbH",
      "::",
      "Distributed",
      "Systems",
      "Engineer",
      "::",
      "Pune",
      "::",
      "Feb",
      "2018",
      "→",
      "Nov",
      "2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "name",
      "=",
      "Thoughtworks",
      "India"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "hotel",
      "revenue",
      "analyst|ITC",
      "Hotels|Kolkata|2020|present|client:LuxurySegment"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Cognizant",
      "|",
      "Graduate",
      "Trainee",
      "|",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "Aug",
      "2016",
      "-",
      "Jul",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Computacenter",
      "|",
      "Systems",
      "Integration",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Hatfield,",
      "Hertfordshire",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "National",
      "Grid",
      "|",
      "2016–2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Regional",
      "Sales",
      "Manager",
      "at",
      "Cognizant",
      "Technology",
      "Solutions,",
      "Dallas",
      "(2021–Present)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech:",
      "Data",
      "Science",
      "@",
      "IIIT",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "2016–2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech,",
      "Information",
      "Technology,",
      "GGSIPU",
      "|",
      "2009-2013",
      "|",
      "80.7%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "I-FIELD",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys",
      "(Client:",
      "UBS)",
      ">>",
      "Sr.",
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      ">>",
      "Pune",
      ">>",
      "2018-2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "TCS"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Cognizant",
      "|",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "2013",
      "to",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Ventures",
      "Investments",
      "Co.",
      "Principal",
      "Data",
      "Scientist",
      "Bangalore",
      "2020/05",
      "-",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "When",
      ":",
      "August",
      "2017",
      "–",
      "June",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sr.",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "ICICI",
      "Bank",
      "Tech",
      "|",
      "Mumbai",
      "|",
      "01/2019",
      "-",
      "03/2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.:",
      "CSE",
      "@",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2011-2015",
      "|",
      "69.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "MEd",
      ";",
      "Delhi",
      "University",
      ";",
      "Delhi",
      ";",
      "2012",
      ";",
      "2014",
      ";",
      "cgpa:7.6/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_START",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "SDE",
      "II"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "[Firm]",
      "~",
      "SendGrid",
      "|",
      "[Title]",
      "~",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "[City]",
      "~",
      "Denver",
      "CO",
      "|",
      "[Client]",
      "~",
      "Mailchimp",
      "|",
      "[When]",
      "~",
      "May",
      "2019-Dec",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "December",
      "2022",
      "-",
      "Current"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DATE_START",
      "I-DATE_START",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "previouslydataScientist",
      "persistentsystems",
      "pune2017-2020",
      "client:dropbox"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "degree",
      "=",
      "M.Tech",
      "CSE"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Platform",
      "Dev",
      "|",
      "San",
      "Francisco",
      "CA",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Azure",
      "|",
      "Oct",
      "2019-Mar",
      "2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-DATE_START",
      "B-DATE_END",
      "I-DATE_END"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "Telecommunications",
      "~",
      "RVCE",
      "Bangalore",
      "~",
      "2013",
      "~",
      "79.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Work",
      "Location.......",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Anna",
      "University",
      ">",
      "B.Tech",
      "Electronics",
      ">",
      "2010-2013",
      ">",
      "90%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-FIELD",
      "O",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "O",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.,",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Mumbai,",
      "2014,",
      "70%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "I-INSTITUTION",
      "B-EDU_YEAR_END",
      "B-GRADE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Associate",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Cognizant",
      "|",
      "Chennai,",
      "Tamil",
      "Nadu",
      "|",
      "08/2017",
      "-",
      "12/2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
